Yeah, they won't stop
Yeah, well
You know there is a difference in the algorithm with the soft a I don't I don't treat the algorithm
I don't I don't you guys move you're gonna debate about hard a soft a
Just because he said you know people say that okay, I don't like it, but
They might say that I don't it's different than that hard ER that is said form of or
Inverbump, but just because oh
Well, they said this so I should be able to say this I mean stop stop I and I just asked you don't say that right I
Just yeah, you don't say the horror. Yeah, he doesn't he never does
So but I had just asked you to I just told you I just told you and you know you knew how to say it to you
I did I told you again, and then you said it again, but then I'm mad
But you know who does it that Alex?
And Alex, you know
Yeah, I
Know man, it's like this really I mean
It's none of their business you're medical.
I mean, it's like, I don't know why, I just don't know.
See, the same kind of thing was happening
with Hannah and them, with like kind of RG and Amanda.
I see, I mean, I'm putting together,
there's some kind of weird, what is this,
with like, oh, oh, you have cancer?
Like, what do these people do?
I don't know, but like, Black RG,
I do see a correlation kind of like, you know,
Why are you going after like a
Someone
Can't I don't understand and my father had cancer and so it's like it's really not funny to me. It's like
it's like, you know, it's really offensive and
Why is it and why is it even like a she just
I know you I know RG and you have but I mean, I don't think it's appropriate to be going after
Um, I just don't know there might be a history or might be I don't know
I clearly can't get into all the details, but it's like even
Chasing a man around the whole time. Let me see. Like I already said, he was gonna come after me several other ladies told me
He made some uncomfortable. Yeah, people people are uncomfortable with stuff with this stuff, right?
Scream louder who's screaming
Poise, you know, but I'm not screaming I can I can show you screaming, but you weren't here JT
Sure, you let your guy come up and start but
You can't say shit. You can talk in the chat. You can talk in the chat, but it's like it's too much. I mean, it's like
I don't know. I
You know, I'm friends with Sam and like I know Sam and you know, I'm yeah, yeah
He hasn't been blocked. So it's like, yeah, just be in the chat
and blocking it anybody in the chat and says if you'll never see it or
But when what's the point, it's just talking in circles about the same. It's like just not my show. It's like it's turning into the you're trying to make it a DT show.
Okay. Okay. Well, I just don't like it. Why isn't my show that's like the staging ground for the conflict is not going to it's not going to do anything between you're not going to fix.
I don't know. It's just going to go back and forth forever and all we'll do is hurt my show, right?
Why?
Why not about
It's like all I'm saying is to stop it's like
Comment if you comment up here. Oh, hey, I'm on panel. There's a bubble
Take you know if I don't buy one on the panel me on the panel if I don't it's up to me
You know you think you can have your own panel run your own show say whatever you want in your show
I've never seen that guy unless you come here. He's apparently been asking around about you. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, I don't understand it's like I'm not gonna go if you have a show I'm not gonna go
Oh, I okay. I need a lot of people in your chat. You're gonna be like, well, go away. Go away. Like don't go in my chat then
But you know, I don't know not not talking to you. I mean
If you don't like but it's like then I'm here other stuff. Oh, well, yeah, they're posting and go come come come to this
So, I don't know
Just it's not freeing good thing. Oh check out this cool show. Do you know nothing complimentary or thing? Oh, look at this
Here's some some idiots have the show. Let's go attack everyone there, right?
I don't know, JT, I mean, I don't know.
And then you're on a gay man's panel saying that too.
I mean, it's like, even if I'm not offended by it, definitely.
Just like not, I don't know why people do that.
Alex did the same thing.
I care about you too, Amanda, I love you.
And it's like, he's actually shared your show with people.
Yeah, he shared my show, but.
People saw people saw was we'll see what's really going on. Okay. Yeah
Yeah, you shared the show
Did that did that do any just for my show?
I just had a bunch of people coming in here causing more chaos and then you're laughing about it
You got he's laughing about it and you know your show I have to end the stream because of the porn bomber or something
Just type whatever you want in the chat. You're okay
Yeah, go say whatever you want in the chat
You know, I'm I'm I'm guys. I'm sorry the panel is gonna be a little bit tighter. Okay
It's just like there's just too much. It's just too much ending the streams
To which unnecessary drama
Yeah, so I have to tighten it up. I'm sorry. So it's like, you know, if you you know
Panel is like, you know, it's like the stage it's like this and it's like the center stage for the show and you know
I really need to follow the rules in the panel in the chat the rules are kind of like, you know a little bit less serious the panel
It's on it's on the video action. I
Love the drama. I really don't I mean I really would like I'd like to heal
But it's like it seems like okay. Well, this is never gonna resolve. It's all it's gonna do is hurt me. Okay
Okay
Start your own panels. Do say whatever you want make more videos and you know that other people have it on your channel
But why does it have to affect my channel? Okay?
Why does it affect my channel?
JT why is it why you have to pick my channel?
Yeah, oh, that's what I'm saying. I'm going to but it's like, you know, I was trying to resolve it and like I was gonna be like, okay
I'm gonna I'll uh, you know, you promise to follow the rules. Yeah, you know, we'll be fine
I'll I'll hide your account even though you felt it called me weak and guys call me weak and you're just insulting me
Phase one phase two of the instruction plan. Let's clap this channel. Okay. Oh, yeah, I
Could I get can overlook it, but
Then you start saying
Something I just told you I just asked you I just I just asked you Alex was the same. No, it's like
Alex is the same way. It's the kind of this thing where it's like, no, they can't they won't they won't change
Yeah, and make you guys making fun of cancer patients is like low
It's low. I
Understand she posted maybe a photo on her Facebook. Okay?
of her a scar
Just because someone has a photo on Facebook does that mean you can go to anybody's Facebook take their picture off
Take any pictures. I want make videos of what was it on their Facebook? I
Don't know I don't know what you can make it sound ridiculous, but there's something going on. There's some kind of like
weird
Then we all show up at the same time
Everyone's it's just weird
Yeah, I mean
The show has to be fun for me to continue to do it
It's like if you're trying to make it not fun for me if you're trying to
Bother me it's like what you're not doing anything besides that if you see is bothering me and you see that's I'm asking you please stop
During the show
You say oh, I didn't mean to do that. I'm sorry
right
not like
Continue to argue. Oh this is
Sometimes, you know, it's like, oh, it's the thing that rules aren't applied completely fairly. I try to be as fair as possible
I try to apply the rules evenly sometimes. Don't miss a comment. Sometimes there won't be a mod that gets a comment
I don't know exactly all the drama or what's being said necessarily
Um, I can't worry about that other stuff to worry about the mods of other stuff to worry about. We're trying good good
Congratulations. I hope there's a lot more charators. So
Yeah
So, you can go anywhere, but it's not appropriate here, okay?
I'm reaching the end of my patient.
I'm a very patient person, very patient.
I was hoping that we could, like, you know, you get to know me and some people here.
Okay, you know, we're cool.
But it's like you just...
And that says, okay, let people up here on screen act guitar.
You're going to get more drunk.
Okay, I'm trying to get less and so I'm trying you know, I want I want less drama. I don't mind a little drama
You know, it makes it interesting. It's fun. Sometimes I like controversy and stuff
but this is the storyline is the story line is a
Getting your stale. That's the way numerous people that okay, I
Okay, so it's medical his her medical history is none of our business. It's that's her business and
What does it matter, RG, like, no?
Who's screams up there every single time?
Oh, definitely, okay.
Hold on, what is this, Whiskey River Tarot?
No, I'm not dropping the link for you.
You are a bomber.
I know who you are, Blackout Andy 3.
Yes, you are you were just up on panel. Yes, I just let you on
Morning psych first of all I apologize for my behavior earlier. I get it was out of bounds
Out of bounds of good taste or whatever this thing with Amanda and you're right
I'll let you talk first since you're not gonna stop. Let me go ahead and post this
Okay, here we go. Can you make that big for me, please?
Why? Why does that matter?
Okay, that is my MRI in July. If you make it bigger and click on it, then I immediately leave MRI.
So you're sympathy-baiting. I get it.
I got a surgery oncology at my next appointment after I have my MRI now
Why would I be going to surgery oncology for a man that listen listen listen? Okay?
If you yeah, if you do have cancer, you know that sucks and I'm sorry I brought it up
Okay, no one it's a awful horrible thing and no one deserves to go through it even if I don't like you
I don't you want to know the story RG. No, you want to stop for a minute so I can speak. Thank you
I was told by numerous people that about a year ago, you faked a whole cancer thing and it was
exposed in your community. It was a whole big thing. That's the only reason why I brought it up.
Are you going to let me finish or no? You started all of this with me. You started,
you thought I didn't get on panel. I think he's referring to Bruno. Bruno faked a cancer. That's
all I know. Do you want the truth or do you want what somebody else told you?
Listen, you start shit with with people and man to think that they're not going to defend yourself.
Four years ago, I had part of my movement.
You started shit with the wrong person because I will defend myself.
No, I'm going to tell this story and I'll tell everybody's listening.
You can't come up here and cry, boo-hoo!
Four years ago, I had part of my movement.
You started this.
RG, you said you said she lied about it so that she proved to you.
I was fine.
You can tell the story.
I'm going to tell the story.
Four years ago.
I had part of my liver removed.
I had 30% of it removed because I have liver cancer, okay?
And when I came back,
that fucking troll community could not handle the fact.
I was a liar.
I didn't have cancer.
You don't sound sick.
You don't do this.
You don't do that.
So I showed them a fake picture of a piece of a liver
that came off of my friend's surgery.
And that is what.
Just say, you know what?
It was a misunderstanding.
And I won't bring it up anymore.
And then I have proven to them time.
To say I just made this up out of nowhere
is fucking insane. But I have cancer.
I've literally proven it to them.
Okay, you have cancer. I'm sorry you're going through this.
Sorry. I mean, y'all need to leave me the fuck alone about it.
Well, Amanda, you started this.
You didn't think I would up on that one.
So you decided to go run your mouth about me to other communities.
You may- I don't talk about you anywhere.
Yes, you do. I don't care about you.
What community? What community, Amanda?
Other women feel very uncomfortable around you. Black Archie. I don't know you
But I'm telling you you're very forceful and you need to know shit. It's sweet tits
I'm not your sweet tits. We don't know each other. We're not on that level
Yeah, she is sympathy baby that's besides support I don't need
What
Anybody
Period I don't need you motherfuckers to hold my hand
Thank you for that, but I don't I don't use my channel this
Allegedly show what he's trying to
you look exactly how you sound though by the way woman Jesus that picture was
taken four years ago video do you know that I had 65% of my stomach removed do
you think I still look like that I don't know man use your brain I don't know
you've heard cancer it can move in metastasize you've mentioned the word
cancer 50 times since you've been up here
Well, you're the one that seems to know so much.
So I'm telling you the fact is I made a joke
because this is what I was told.
Apparently it was a misunderstanding.
And if you don't want to talk about it,
let's not talk about it.
Let's not bring up the word cancer.
Then quit telling me that I sound like I look.
I had 65% of my stomach removed.
I don't look that way anymore.
She's sympathy baiting.
We get it.
I apologize.
Shut the fuck up.
I'm not sympathy baiting for shit.
Oh, that's a lie.
My god, you have issues dude leave me an awful awful human. I dislike you greatly. I don't care. I think you're glad
No one else likes you either
I
You thought I I didn't go up on panel, but guess what you were wrong
Sweetie that's Janet how much of a stalker I am. I don't know Janet and I don't care
Well, you should meet her you two would make a hell of a team. I
Mean apparently you need to reevaluate your life is your stock
Why cuz I have a fun hobby
A fun hobby dude, you said that.
Stalking people on the internet is a fun hobby.
It absolutely is.
How to tell me you're a psychopath
without telling me you're a psychopath.
Yes, there's lines, there's lines.
You know, there's lines.
Let's see what you look like.
That's me in my picture right there, honey.
That's not your picture.
What do you mean it's not my picture?
It's absolutely his white picture.
It's somebody's picture of hands.
Hands it's me covering my face exactly of hands. Why don't you cam up since you're the most beautiful? Why would I do that?
Why would I cam up because you asked me to?
I see women
That is stock Janet. Yeah, and before that Jimmy Wow, you think you're trying to make some type of moral point you had
Wow, that's pathetic. It really is why why is it?
Why she did the same thing you know what Amanda Amanda she did the same thing you did
She invited this she brought us into her life kind of like you did up here on Sykes
Okay, well the fact is you're just not as interesting as that's the fact of the matter. You're a bore
You have an issue that you need to get some help apparently maybe you know
Depends on what side of the coin you're on
I think you're sociopath.
Maybe, maybe.
It just might be.
Anyway, so I it looks like you disappeared. Thank you for letting me up and I showed the picture and explained it
I'm gonna change my explain anything
What why did this do? Why did this whole entire community think that you were faking something as awful as cancer?
And again, I apologize that you have it
I think it's an awful thing that nobody should go through
If you can't accept it, that is your problem, please. You just thought you're an awful person
You're an awful awful trash fire human believe them please. I
Mean, there's a lot of them saying it Amanda
And they all told me they even called my fucking doctor's office, okay, that's all I would never do that's awful
So why don't you listen say they only tell you one side of the coin you see
I talked to one guy specifically that you you said a lot of awful shit about uh
So he just gave me the i'm not gonna say who but he kind of gave me the the lowdown on you and that was
believe it like it's gospel.
Why didn't they take it?
I've known them for four or five years now.
They've called my hospital and trying to get my medical records.
I didn't call your hospital.
Why would I do such a thing?
I said they did.
Since they're such...
How is that my fucking fault?
Since they're such upstanding people that you believe.
You don't know who they are.
They're for the upstanding people you believe.
You don't know who the person is. I heard that doesn't matter. He said you've done some horrible things to him
Actually said some nasty nasty things
So my advice would be that you invite this stuff into your life because you invited me into your life
Did you somebody name big fucking fat mouth in you? You invited me into your life?
I don't know who Moshe is and that's who you mentioned. So apparently that's correct
He's a good. He's a good general. He's a gentleman in his scholar. I don't even know who he is
He knows you know he doesn't I think I think you invite this stuff into your life Amanda
That's what I think you invited me into your life. You're just lucky. I'm busy with Janet at the moment
You look like a fool you got information from people that stalked me and stalked my doctor. Oh boo who?
You have an issue dude. You need
And I hope and I wonder why I didn't know
Care to fucking know you the FBI or whoever and deals with you because
Crystal on the call the white house. I mean plenty other people call the FBI too, but listen Amanda
I didn't know you I didn't care to know you you invited me into your life, man
I mean, it's not hard for me to believe that you invited the other but the other trolls in your life, too
It's just your wonderful personality. It's believe them like it's a gospel
No, I didn't all I'm saying is people are fucking with you because you're inviting it
I don't hang with those people. I haven't seen some of my guys. She's not getting it. Are you this fucking daft?
Are you this dense?
You shoot you shoot your fucking mouth off and you wonder why people come at you
You know who you are you're stalking a woman on the internet who Janet. Yeah, well
Woman is you know, that's to be determined. She's an awful awful person
As well because they've come to me and told me who
Who came to you came to you and told you told you about me
You're full of shit. That's why
Fuck would you I fuck with Groovy Jimmy and then Janet who just became a side character a Groovy Jimmy and that's it
I mean, do you just shoot your mouth off?
Do you have a job and you're living your mom's basement like are you an in-sale?
What is your problem?
Yeah, you got me. You got me.
This is where I started this in the first place, Amanda.
No, what started it is you're a little man in a big boat.
No, no, what started it was you were on a Sykes panel talking all types of shit to chat.
You didn't get in the lit when I looked at them.
You banned half this fucking chat because you couldn't pull in a little me.
I would pull in me and my feelings.
You didn't even tell me about yourself.
You were a fucking Karen.
You're a Karen, you know what nobody even look like a fucking Karen and you can sit down in your basement with your five
Okay, okay. Oh my basement. You got me
Then you fucking show up at my fucking door fat boy. I
I'll be surprised if you could move really
Also be surprised if anyone's touched you in the last fucking half a quarter century
I just got out of the shower, but yet I can't
You look exactly how you sound there
That's just it my point is Amanda if you want to have better relations
Maybe I wouldn't invite this into your life
And your associate path and I'm done with this
This might be true. I don't know I've heard both depends what side of the coin you're on
She is awful awful awful person and again, she invites us into her life and apparently I'm not the first person
That's happened with I'm not she challenged a whole other apparently the one as far as the color doctor's office
Which I think is awful, but
You can't sit there and challenge people and then go
When you know they show a picture of your fat-looking face you just you can't just shut your mouth to be be more pleasant Amanda
Be more fucking pleasant
Hello, yeah, hey, what's up, dude?
Okay, well you see like this is like hi, hi Amanda. Yeah, I know man
It's just like a it's just so weird. I don't I
Don't know. I don't know why I don't know why
People have animosity. I don't know people are mad at me. Sometimes it's like there seems like no reason. I don't still know
Okay, so
You have a conversation, okay
the
Yeah, well, we can choose to we can choose to move on
I mean if I can still if I have a problem with you if you promise not think you know stop
You know and you have pretty much, but just stop stop the dog. Yeah, I'm good. It's like you I'm good
But when people come up here and start yelling at me and antagonizing me
Yeah, people that people will people will then people okay, and then I'm gonna say something
Well, I mean I say something too, but yeah, it's like, you know, sometimes it's I don't say something because I know it's not used all
You gotta understand. I'm not I come from a community where nothing is PC people say anything and everything
Yeah, then you should then you said so if you come from that community, you shouldn't be offended by every like little thing
I'm not I'm not the one who was offended. You're playing with the dog
See and stuff like that you're in you're doing it
And so people are gonna like be mad and like and have a reaction towards it because you're and I told you I'm not gonna use the pictures
Okay, I can't post links because I'm not a mod. Okay told you. Yeah, and okay
I'll try to keep a better eye on the chat if I see anything like
Put personal but personal information which I've never seen anything personal about you if I if I reduce it
I'll
Delete it. You can put it right to my attention. You have my discord, too
Yeah, we watch and then watch the language and it's like you have to and it's like at least respect the panel
You're like, oh, what do you know? I am I am producing a show. I am like also
We're jerking off back there. I don't know what the fuck you were doing. Honestly, that's producing
Well, if I you know if I want to jerk off I probably just end the stream I
It's kind of like kind of like to a
Too crazy to like leave leave unattended. No, I mean do you ever just need a break?
You just go back there and jerk off to get away from the fucking maniacs like
No, no, I don't need to jerk off
Kidding, but no really though. It's a lot. I mean
I mean, it's gonna happen on every panel you're gonna have motherfuckers up your screaming, but Jesus though
Like there's certain ones that that's all they do
Right, but it's like, you know, there are people that it can be very quiet
But so antagonizing and they they can be quiet and calm and get people upset
Who didn't antagonize me? Okay. Well, it's like, you know, I can't figure out who is the first I can't go back
And I'm not here to like, yeah, I don't bog you down. Do I cover psyche? Let me give you a whole fucking history less
I don't know a bunch of people that
Why would you care about any of that?
I don't care. I don't I don't that's why I don't
Here's what I care about care about my show I care about having like a show it's safer people like people can come in
They say oh, this is a nice place. I can hang out. I can meet nice people not they come in and they're like
Oh, what the fuck is going on this?
They're talking about creating. Yeah, when you run up your screening. Yeah, I'm using this shit for content
Yeah, like what the fuck is anybody supposed to think like?
I get it. Well, I mean that's I mean the same and six I know so I know his personality and that's that's kind of like
You know how he had how his show is and so he has a show that's more about some of that stuff than mine
And you know, maybe it would be more appropriate to like any years is your show to do that
What do you think he's clipping like I mean you must know because my show my show does produce content
But it's like I'm not trying to really produce but it's fine
It's fine facial produces content and people like my content and it's provocative
But it's just it can't be just saying and somebody's got to use your show to make their fucking content
Like what the fuck is that about? Well, I mean it's like some people are
Channels that comment or commentary channels and they comment on footage and they talk about footage and stuff and that's content too
They create so you go up here and start shit with people so you can record it and make content with the fucking
I'm not supposed to say anything
Yeah, I'm gonna say something if he comes up here talking shit to me every single time I will
It's pretty he's pretty innocuous. I mean, it's like, you know, he's someone innocuous
Yeah, because he is because he can't do shit, but still you're gonna come and talk shit to me
I'm gonna say something to you
Yeah, and I'm not real I'm not real pc. Yeah, I'm not like
Okay, but but it's like, you know, I would say I would say if you're gonna get into argument stuff
You're gonna do it. I don't know. You don't you don't see me running up here talking about people people people get people get to
To uh, I mean I have to people are getting too excited on the panel and saying things they shouldn't be
That's what you're gonna
Yeah, but it's so I mean so maybe it's like, you know, it's better just to have you on the panel
Just you know, you maybe you without other people, you know, it's like I don't I just don't look man
I'm not bringing you anybody's I'm not coming up here talking shit to people. I'm not coming up here talking about people
If I'm all fuckers gonna talk crazy to me, I'm gonna talk crazy back. Yeah, but it's like you but you present yourself
That is yours. It's totally innocent person just being attacked
You're playing around in this stuff and you're doing on my channel and I you know
It's like I just ask you to stop and you if you read then it's like just do it
I can't post links and I don't change pictures anymore. I told you I would
No problem then as long as you watch the language, I don't have a problem with you, but and I'll
I'll be the language. Yeah, I work on the language. You know, I'm not used to that. Don't just just don't say it
You know, it's like, you know, just remember when you're in church or something like that when you're here and then use that kind of
I don't know. You're really fucked up church, but yeah, I'll try
Well, you know, or a nice restaurant or something place some place you wouldn't want a nice restaurant
I wouldn't have a motherfucker screaming at me and shit on the top of his lungs every time I every time I'm on panel
Yeah, but you know, I'm saying like and I'm not saying like
Screaming but you're yelling at the F4 you're really at the GGOC on a gay man's panel. Okay, look, man, you know
If I had anything against gay people, I wouldn't be here, you know, okay
I know I'm not offended but I'm saying, you know, just have some self-awareness like hey
I'm uh, I'm on somebody else's panel. First of all, I'm on
I'm actually on a
Tarot channel spiritual channel that is trying to have a positive message and ultimately even though there is drama
I like people to make up and stuff. Maybe it doesn't always work, right?
But it's just not it's just like it just so out of place y'all showed up and then all this stuff started happening
And it's like it's just and everyone's I'm telling me you didn't have any type of drama before we came
Oh, I did but it was like but this but it was like kind of like more steamed to the show at least you know
It was like, you know, it's just like it just was out of the blue
just a bunch of people showed up and
All and they all started doing the same thing and they're all from the same and then they're talking and then they're talking
like like like I'll just be some collateral damage that they're
They do it for fun and they they do it to done it before they laugh at it. They
And then you're back to stage four. Yeah, when everybody's acting like I'm in the fucking moment
Well, yeah, I mean, I know that that was alex and he you know, what the fuck
I mean, I mean alex is, you know, major conspiracy and you know, I he wasn't making sense. I mean, I know
But maybe he's not the only one acting like that though
I mean just just because he said just because he said oh, it's because it's some some anti gay church
You know that made sense to him at the time, you know, it doesn't doesn't I you know, I never is that oh, yeah
You're right alex, but doesn't mean that
I don't want to tell you that I'm trying to take your channel or whatever the hell
So I understand if I have
You guys are telling me yourself you guys are saying the chat and you're like, oh, we're just joking about it's not funny to
Joke about like it's like you're used to
You think I'm supposed to laugh at you talking about like you think about it logically men
Why would I bring a bunch of people here to bitch about me? What sense would that even make?
What I don't I didn't see them bitching. I guess I see most of my
You there my mods were just concerned. They're like
The people that came I have no idea who they are and again
You bought me recently a lot a lot a lot right let's not let's not beat around the bush here
You brought a lot you brought a lot of people here, right? You just know I'm not saying I brought them saying that they came here to bitch about me
I don't why would I bring people here to bitch about me? What's with that man? I don't think you did. I don't think you did
I don't I didn't yeah, that doesn't make any sense
I see a lot of you doing high-fives of people. I don't know that you brought you brought here
Okay, so it's like it just has nothing to do with me and I'm really done with it
So, you know, we can change the topic tarot. Let's do some let's do something something fun
No, we can but I just want to make sure like, you know, let's just like
I don't know, but I have to say that if it continues, I just can't, I can't, if I even have to do no panels, I'll do no panels in the future, but I like doing panels and you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you laugh, you
Because it's not fun for me anymore. It's not fun for anybody. It's it's my people are getting how do you feelings?
I haven't all all my friends like you know say I'm a terrible person because I let people say things on panel or on the show
You're not a bad person. You're not that's what I mean. That's what I mean told. That's what I mean
Oh, I'm not even just a bad person. I'm like some scum of the earth. You're not a bad person
I don't I know I know I'm not I know I'm not but this is what people are
This is what the odd like some in the audience and my friends are now saying and it's because
Not just because of you, but I mean there's a lot of people and I'm not saying that I'm perfect and I've done
The perfect
You brought it to the you but you guys brought it to the tipping point you guys made you guys brought it right up right
Right, it's just exacerbating it. I understand that but the point is you can't please
Everybody
Let me let me please myself it'll please myself if I have a nice panel where it's not just about you and
Doxy and constantly I know I'm being attacked in chat. I mean, yeah, so stop talking about it
I don't want to hear about it anymore, right? Yeah, I agree. Okay, so if there shouldn't be an issue
It's like if that even people come in it's like who cares if people say on the chat if someone comes on the panel
Start talking about you and you're here. I'll put you on the panel or I'll probably take them off
Because I don't like people talking about people when they're not here, okay?
So I mean but and I'll let you have a debate with somebody has something to say
But it's like in the chat, you know the chat is kind of like
Look, I get that it's less it's less important than the panel the chat is like a lot of people say a lot of things
I have mods burning the the chat. I need to run the panel. Okay. I'm the only one that can do it. So
Let me run my panel. Let me have how do I want on stage when I want bringing people up, you know
Don't be offended if I don't bring you up
Don't that goes for every look so the one night when I said I'd come back later
That wasn't me being offended. That was me saying I'll just come back later. Okay, I just did I do it too
Well, when I you know, I don't always want everybody up at the same time sometimes
I don't want certain people up right now at the certain. It's fine. I don't take that personal
You don't have to explain all that to me. I don't I don't want taking that person. I mean, but it's like I just
Constantly I'm getting oh, why did you do this? Why'd you just I'm like
Because because it's my show I
Yeah, that goes so it's open if it's you think people think it's fair is not fair this and that
You know, but there's fair not fair. I'm I'm running my show like I want to run my show and you can bring things to my attention
I can consider things but
I can't just I mean I get so many
I guess so many letters a day all not about just a lot about just me
Okay, I mean you have been in a few messages, but a lot of people are messages for doing stick a lot
And so it's like I'm really trying to grant you it's just not I understand
You're trying to be fair and you can't and it's making it. It's like if you I get it
it's impossible to try to be fair you can 100% it's it's you know life isn't fair like things
are unfair sometimes it's impossible to be a hundred percent well you're in a position where
you got a it's like everybody wants something
Right, and it's like, you know, if everybody wants something, you know, it's like I'm here offering people a platform to like come and chat on to come on
The panel and and talk about right I'm offering I'm offering and so I and it's like but I can't I said the panel the panel is kind of like
And the thing is the more the numbers grow the more that kind of stuff is gonna like that's yeah
That's why I'm tight. That's why I tighten it up now
That's why I need to tighten it up now because it's like I have to but it's like, you know, you and God you kind of
Chuckling about oh look it's going out of control and you're enjoying the chaos when I'm laughing
It's because I'm laughing at how ridiculous it is not because not at your expense
But how ridiculous it is that you I have so many people coming in here
Trying to create chaos about me when all i'm doing is just sitting up here talking to you if you think it's ridiculous
How fucking religious do you think it's right? Do you think I think oh you must think it's really? Yeah, I think it's like
I think it's um, it's well. Yeah, it's ridiculous, but it's like it would be more
If they weren't if they weren't putting my channel at jeopardy, it would be ridiculous. Otherwise. It's just maliceous or
Some kind so
Look man, if I was monetized like you and motherfucker even mentions like I'm gonna take your channel down
They're fucking gone. It's how I mean, I'm not telling you how to run your shit. But yeah
I don't give a fuck what it's about
Yeah, so so with that logic, so I should uh, I should block gaudy then because gaudy was like, oh
The night gaudy struck um
Stike's channel. I mean if you you have a feel for people
I have a feel for people but you're also i'm very like you know forgiving and I also see the good in people and I like people
Be honest with me. I like I like to believe I like to believe that people aren't as malicious
But it seems like sometimes they are go ahead
Be honest with me psyche. What is your real impression of me? No bullshit. I'm not going to be mad
What do you I mean? No, no, what is your actual impression? I feel I feel like you okay?
Well, I don't think I don't think you care for me very much. I don't think I think I think I'm pretty mean
I think I'm pretty I'm just I'm just happy to be here. How about my platform?
I'm collateral damage, but if I'm taking out it doesn't do any of you. Oh, that's what you've been told
You don't care. You won't care if my channel. Did you care what you'd be saying? Hey, what's upside?
Can I how can I help you? No, no
Listen, there's a difference between me not caring and me wanting your channel to be gone
Okay, so the truth is if you're looking at the time you're getting look look at all the time you're getting on my channel
Are you a member of my channel? Are you a member of my channel? Look at all the time you're getting
Are you a member?
No, I know there's other people that I can decide that other people do other things there's other things
I'm just trying to think what have you done to
Help the channel support the channel like is there anything in every reason why she's taking up so much time
So much time on my show so much time of energy and problems just like alex was right and he was and I kept defending him
Hey, he's a good guy. He's a guy. He turns on me just over nothing, right? So
So yeah, so anyway
Yeah, the truth is if your channel went down, there's a difference between me wanting your channel to go down and me not caring if it goes down
So you wouldn't care. Okay, so so so you don't care about my show. So you don't
Fine, no, no, but okay, so there's a difference in you not liking this out or
No, you just said it you just said it
Let me talk so what's the difference between you wanting to take down my show and you're not caring if my show goes on
So tell me the difference
Big difference one is I actually want your channel to be gone, which I don't I would prefer you you have a channel
So yeah, the the other one is if your channel gets taken down
That's not in my control, but it's not something I'm gonna lose sleep about either
You can show it's not in your control. What if my channel is taken down because of something you guys do?
Yeah, I wouldn't be I'm not doing I would it because you're doing things that are against TOS
And I've asked you not to and you keep you guys keep doing it and then you're doing other stuff
I don't even know what the fuck you're doing, but there's just not you're not doing anything that it's supporting the channel
So you don't care about my channel. Why do I care about you? Okay?
Hey, did you why do I care about you?
Why why do I care if you're on the panel or not?
Okay
You don't care. Why do I care?
I care about my show I
Care too much about
People like you that just come here to hurt my show. I don't care about me. Don't care. They just
Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna be and you're I don't want to be associated with like
Doxing cancer patients and and disabled my I don't want to be oh look what he allows on a show. That's not me. Okay, not me
So it's very disturbing that kind of stuff happens, okay, so
JT you can talk and chat you don't need to be on the panel all the time. It's too much time. Okay
He's trying to take down my channel and make
Okay
Whether he's trying but whether he's trying to take down my channel or he's doesn't care if it gets taken down either way
He has no reason no motivation either those scenarios to behave himself, right?
There's no he doesn't have to he he can just do it because it doesn't matter to him if the channel gets taken down
He won't care even if he gets taken down because of some stupid bullshit. He's doing right
Casey here's my impression of you you asked me you're my impression of you my impression of you is you're very polite and
You know cordial and reasonable talking one-on-one where you're doing a bunch of fuck shit, okay?
Okay, you're doing a bunch of fuck shit and you're doing stuff. I don't
Know everything that's going on, but I see enough. I just see um, no, I don't like it. Okay. I
Don't like it. Okay. I'm Miguel
Miguel can you just can you show me yourself on camera? I just need to see it to you. I just need you don't have to okay
Hi, Miguel
Hello, how are you?
I can't type unless hello, but it's black. You can type in the chat
Did you, is it, you think you're blocked or are you just, no, you're gonna, you're gonna, you're gonna one minutes. Yeah, then I can't type.
You can't type? Okay. I'll take, I'll take my list, but you can talk on the panel. I'm sorry. Hold on. Let me see if you're blocked.
Yeah.
I can't type.
Okay, let's see.
What's that?
Okay, Miguel, I don't know if you got timed out or something, but you're not on the block list
So I don't know why you can't type but can you turn on the music?
That's why I say one minute. So I go one minute and I can't time I can't say you know, okay?
Did you just subscribe just now?
No, he's been subscribed
Okay, I'm sorry, Miguel. I think I maybe got timed out by somebody I'm not sure but if somebody sees Miguel timed out and check
Can you just reverse it through 10 seconds and you know, I'm sorry, Miguel. I'm
I don't mean to, I don't know what happened there, okay?
Yeah, I'm not gonna chime on nobody
because I always, they only talk and you know,
sometimes I do my swing and I'm gonna clap my hands
but then I'm not gonna clap nobody anyway, so.
Mm-hmm.
You know?
Okay.
So, that's how this machine works, I confess it,
but it's not my swing, it's just my swing, you know?
Okay, okay.
I hope you fix it.
So, that's how the machine works, you know?
That's how I'm not.
OK, so let me see if people are behaving, you know, sometimes people behave and then they come on to the panel, you know, if not mine, you know.
OK, I'm sorry about that.
It's alright, it's alright.
OK, check it out. OK, OK.
Yeah, I saw about my movie, I watched the movie, that's one. See?
You see the Sacro, you see the movie?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, it's a movie.
I'm on the pastry.
A movie, mm-hmm, okay.
Yeah, let's see.
It's a good movie.
Oh, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Yeah, it's a good movie.
It's a funny movie.
What's it called?
It's called AMC, the movie AMC, that is a good one.
And it's called the blind movie version one, you know.
That's what today I'm going to move on,
or let alone watch my church and I'm going to cry AM.
So, you know.
Okay.
I'm good.
I hope you have a great day.
I'm going to do some streaming at Coney Island soon.
Yeah, I'm not going to Korea right now. I don't know if I'm going to Korea today or in this party.
Let me see how they're going today. I don't know that this is the way.
Okay, good. Yeah, so let's take your time.
You made a moment for yesterday. I had a video, a moment for when we went to yesterday.
I went to do my YouTube channel yesterday the moment for way
Yeah, I want to watch a moment away you go go about watching me play a moment away yesterday
moment away you want to watch me play watch me play
Cool, yeah, it looks like you're
You're uh, it looks like you're doing good. Hope you're doing well. You're glad your stream is going well
You're a cool guy
You know good. Hopefully if a mod or you can post
I think you should be a I thought you were a moderate
But if you if anyone's able to post the link for Miguel's channel
he does live streams at Coney Island, I think pretty often and
Really good and make sure you subscribe to Miguel and say hi. I'm in his chat. Please. Please
Please be nice. Okay. Can you ask him? Oh, yeah, are you are you Miguel? Are you Cuban?
No, no, okay, Puerto Rican
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Awesome.
Yeah.
So, you know,
Glad to see you. It's been a while since you've been on the panel. Glad to see you. Glad you're doing well and
You're a great guy
Other good
yelling and then I kick it out, you know, kick out or not kick out, but you know, my pain is
Yeah
Yeah, you need to learn I probably I could probably learn some things from you about running panels because you know
You seem you seem like you've got it down when they start yelling. Just just take them off, right?
Yeah
You sound like a you sound like a better host than I than I've been so
Pretty good pretty good Miguel. I'm proud of you
give it
Good stream. Congratulations on
You know building up your channel. I really hope
It becomes a great success and you have fun and you go keep doing you and
I want to come I want to come check out your alive. I keep sometimes I miss them, but
Okay, 11 o'clock a.m. Today guys. He's gonna be at Coney Island
Okay, yeah, let us know when you know, okay
Okay, okay
Yeah, and I mean I see I see I think you're having a good conversation with then is in in the back
I really like want you to get that point because you're like, oh
PC bullshit and it's just it's just the rules for you, okay? That's all it is. It's not about
Sensoring or oh, you're not allowed to say it's just for the sake of my channel. Please like I don't say those words, okay?
And I know I know you probably I know you don't care about my it's nice that you just rather rather don't care of my channel
I get taken down rather than actively trying to take it down
But there's really no difference if you're like that means you can act however you want and you're not really worried what happens or not
you know, so
Yeah, I'd rather you're gonna be on the panel at least like
You know care about my show in a little bit. No, I don't I don't I would care about your showing that I like your show
I like to hang out. Yeah, I think
Not a bad place. It's like if it's turning into a hostile place
It's not the chat or show for you. Maybe but you know, I don't think you're bad person. You've been cordial and nice, but
There's some other stuff going on too. Okay, it's just I'm not I'm not like
Not some dumb, okay, you can see stuff going on. Okay, you know why they were changed so the barber knows when to stop
Um, it's like you ask, okay, ask him if he, can you dance to awesome again?
I don't know if he hears, but yeah.
It's like, but it's like, I can't.
If I see, if I see you start getting the, uh, uh, uh, okay.
It won't be because of you.
Don't know because there's different thing. I just don't I don't know if you're trying to like say shit and then
You know, I don't know
The trust isn't there you're new you have to you have to work on gaining some first and so you're kind of monopolizing the whole
Show is that what you wanted? You're like, I don't why do you think I wanted?
Didn't invite the 26 people over here. I don't know. I don't know who did with their frontiers and enemy
I don't know I didn't see anybody really going after you some people, but you're
And it's fine if you go back up for them in the chat. I'm saying on my panel
Don't get upset arguments someone start saying f-a-g-g-o-t
I say don't say that you say again. Oh, well, that's free speech or he's saying he's saying n-i-g-g-a
I can't say n-i-g-g-r. I don't want to have these arguments. I can't want to have these arguments, okay?
Even if it's not against TOS, I don't I don't want it on my show
I will have a every race here. I don't want racial language here. I have every
sexuality I'm talking to
Well, JT's in the back chat
Yeah, I
Have gay people here. I have a lot of people here a lot of different people love a lot of different types of people straight people gay people
transsexual trying, you know
black white Asian
different countries it has to be
nice place not like some it's just turning disturbing and it's like if you
don't see how it's like what you're doing is not disturbing me it's like we
can't we can't come in understanding it's not complicated but yeah I'll behave
in your chat I'll ignore people talking shit about me right next one I'm
Oh, yeah, the back chat or the private chat. Yep. So
I think they're having a good conversation like, you know, I like Denison's a good guy and
He understands he gets he gets where I'm coming from
And maybe he can get through them. I'd like I'd like to resolve things. Okay?
Like to be so it's like hey
We're not like it's not gonna bring harm. You don't have to help me
Just don't harm me and what you're doing is harmful. Okay, even if it's just
You know
Getting in fights and bringing weird people here and stuff. It's it's it's okay
No, I'm talking to myself. Yeah
Yeah, I have JT backstage I go and then isn't are you there? Are you talking to me? Yeah, or okay?
Well, thank you. I mean, it's like you're I like what how you're explaining it
I understand his point where it's like yeah a lot of people do want total freedom and think you should be able to
they don't understand the TOS and the you know
How important this is the channels to me is it doesn't matter to them and it does matter to me. It's like I need to
Protect my channel because it doesn't matter to me. Okay, it does matter to me
Having and making sure that everybody is truly completely fair that are doing weird things
That's not that's not the biggest priority. I need to make sure I
Can't can't do everything at once either it's giving too much when they bring when you bring 26 people here talking shit about you
I don't know who brought them here, but it's chaotic, right?
You put backstage sucks. It's not that bad. It's a private chat. It's a there's alcohol back there
It's just you know, it's not that bad. It's a nice green room
It's a very nice green room. It's a very beautiful digital agreement and
You know, it's like if you get put people get so offended to be put backstage. It's just
People go on Jerry Springer show and not saying this is Jerry Springer or anything
I'm saying for example and now we feel going to Jerry Springer show. They'll say, okay, this is your segment and then
You'll come out to your to your fighting for a couple of segments and then then it's the next segment
It's not gonna be like this whole have the same guests on for weeks and weeks and weeks discussing the same thing
You know, we want to
And I know sometimes I know I need to get better and sometimes we do have repetitive storylines and
Some of the same fuck shit going on. I'm trying to be careful. I said, hey, what a wonderful time of
Docs spending it with all these great people time of the day spending it with all these great people. Thank you
Thank you, Theo
Being honest, okay
Okay, what's
So what's the question? Okay, so let me see. Let me look at your chat. What's the purpose of allowing salmon to be an instigator?
Well, I mean that's I mean that salmon
Has you know has a show he has interesting points and it's like I had him up because it's like there was no counter
There's no really counter to
No, I need to it's in the bait. There should be two sides to the bait. And so
Instigate well, he's an instigator. That's his kind of his personality. That's his show
I mean, it's like so and I know I know if I knew you as instigator and you had a show
But it's like he does it in a different way. He's not I don't think he's
Doing and malicious or you can answer I don't know
I think he's happier about getting your stream shut down than JT. Yeah. Yeah, who's yeah, man. Yeah
You think so? Well, I mean, I mean, I'd be able to kind of celebrated like the Saudis after 9-11, you know
He's like that. Yeah, he was dancing on the band backstage, you know Sam and yeah
Uh, I have to ask easy easy was probably there and it's almost like because he got JT to say the F word
And he got your stream taken down. That was like a double win. Okay?
Well, you know, I have to reconsider, you know, we have we have we're not necessarily like we don't always get necessarily long
We're just you know, colleagues and we're both streamers and you know, but do you normally allow instigators on the panel?
It's like
He's pretty he came up here just to talk shit to JT
Well, you know salmon wants to instigate bullshit and doesn't give a fuck about your channel
Well, I'll have to consider about letting salmon on in the future because you know, but also I had the same report of
Cheering backstage when the show gets taken down
About JT, okay?
That's the same thing. So you guys are all happy. So you guys all don't care. Okay, so it means like maybe I have to be more careful
You know, I'm always like willing to give them benefit benefit doubt, but so long live springer. Yeah, so yeah, let's see
God
Okay, man. Okay. Oh my god. I said what a warm, okay
Yeah, so, you know
Sam and I don't when he did like, you know, I told him don't I don't say a name. Usually he doesn't say names
Usually usually just like start no if you start an argument
It's fine when it gets to the doxing the slander the racial language and the threats. That's not good. And so if it gets
To that point, I don't like that, but he hasn't really gotten to that point
Right Miguel is here. I think Miguel used to there. He was bragging about doxing everybody backstage
After you started in your life
Okay, that's why I I need people like you know people like you watching and like letting me know these things because
No, I also would never know because you know, it's just but it's just like but just like Sam
I might be nice to my face and like nothing tape will be on my back
The same thing can be happening, you know, I'm very suspicious like, you know, Ziggy came to me very very
You know, oh, I talked to I talked to JT and rent and they said you're such an awesome person
So I really like you now. I'm sorry if I
by setting them, and it's just like, okay,
well, that seems a little bit disingenuous.
I don't know, it just seems a little bit,
it seems like they're kind of being nice, right?
My face, and then laughing at my back,
or not even when I think my back is starting laughing, right?
Because there were search you're talking shit in chat and they're doing all the talking PDF putting my name with PDF putting
All these different names of PDF. Yeah, and I said my gut is that some feels I don't feel like something's right
Do you have to force your way on into my show?
Like you really have to really that big of a deal if you you're just think that you're arguing about why do I do this?
Why do I do that? It's not really your business how I
Deal with every other guess. It's like I can deal with the guests on an individual basis, right?
I see someone's not right, or doesn't feel right.
Don't have the right to, so.
Yeah, I kinda wanna throw it out there too.
If someone's bullying you or instigating.
The best thing you can do is to be quiet and not react. Yeah, it creates a vacuum for their energy
And it also platforms that highlights their misbehavior for other people watching
Yeah, if you react in kind no one can tell who the good guys and that's why I go back stage sometimes so, you know, I don't
Hasho reaction or
You know, I don't I don't want them to like
Fight be fighting so much to get each other riled up that they would start reacting with each other and then they start coming
To the racial language the dogs. That's where it gets too far and that's it being comes pick it
But was that's just arguing who was just like missed disagreements. That's one thing
It's going to these other dangerous illegal levels, but and it's like won't affect them
It will just affect me in a negative way and they can't do anything good for me
They only hurt hurt me in a bad way. Okay, then isn't it always good along, but he is a good advice. He does
Oh, babe, I'm drinking a drink. So yeah, I mean, I've been drinking too. I mean, this show is it can be stressful
And it's like it'd be really hot. You know, it's hard dealing with so many different personalities
People that don't even care and I put I I care I do care. I do care. I don't know only about my show
But I care about the people here. So
Get your advice here. Well read people and are not fools
Yeah
You're a vicious cyber person a vicious cyber person get your advice from well read people and not pools. Yeah, so
You know
I'm gonna take a deep breath. It's just been too. It's been very very stressful. It's like
Everyone's on my ass, you know, even my friends to my friends the people that hate me
The friends the hardest right telling me I'm just
garbage, you know
It's like you just laughing at me. Oh, I do Karen. Are you suck at their terror reader? Oh
Oh, you know, you know and but about but but about Tracy the three months to go
She's bringing up all this
irrelevant craft that should
Worked out forever ago. I don't know in it. I'm garbage
What are we supposed to oh isn't isn't you know
Don't doesn't he love me aren't they you know, she must she must be right about him. Aren't they close friends? It hurts more from a
from a friend than enemy
Enemies you kind of know what to expect friends kind of comes to the shock, right?
How are my cats? They're good. Where's their kitty cat around? I think they're all outside right now
There's I saw an orange tail. Yeah. Yeah, I think he was out here of tricks is over there
Yeah, projecting emotions are hard to read. Yeah, yeah, and
These are yielding me for getting her dress sent six months ago. Yeah, I
Don't know. I don't know. I hope I hope she like
Feels better. I don't know. I don't know what I did. I hope I didn't
Get her angry and sad or something
Okay, let me see what's going on backstage that constitutes is me calling for pfd's apparently people are literally saying it okay, so
Okay, JT
It's not the show for it. It's not because I don't want to keep going back and forth about oh, they're calling me pdf
How about like now when no one gets called pdf and that's it. You know, it's like that's that's the rule
I don't know why it's like
People you bring in a camp all it, you know, I don't know you were you were saying the same stuff in my chat yesterday, okay?
It's not it's not right for anybody, you know, I'll be mad I'll bring to my attention that person did it instead of reacting to them
Say tell me hey that person said this and I'll go I'll go
Delete their comment and time then okay?
You know he ended the sheen because of the F word, right? Yeah, you know, yeah
And I've done it several times the past few days, right?
And then I had to do it,
then I told you not to do it and you did it again in a minute.
So it's like, is that trustworthy?
Have it on the panel, Titi?
Before that, it was because he wasn't sure
if he was gonna get doxed.
Yeah, so don't, yeah.
Exactly, I mean, I don't think he really cares.
It's like, or else he'd be like, okay, he said, sure, okay.
Well, if he can come to an agreement,
but it shouldn't be just an argument, okay?
Should be I asked you something. Hey, it's my channel. Here's the rules if you want to be here if you don't
You don't follow the rules. You don't have to be here. I
Know your whole argument. Yeah, right? You're not always opposed to have like
Having the fairness challenge either from what I can see you shut it down when someone does something to threaten the stream
Yeah, yeah, and then let me say man up like I like I said like I didn't he never talks to my on my channel before like
He has like come up
He was up once before like trying casing around Q trying to get you know
Maybe content and Q kept coming down that was the other one time and other times he comes in just other people come in
Try to stir the pot to you and
You know I
Mean he does but
It wasn't really to the harmful doxing level that I saw but as soon as it did go there
I ended the stream you saw that so I told her I told him to stop right?
Yeah
Yeah, I see I see I have to think a lot about that you know because I've always
I've always liked him and appreciated him as a content creator and like to show and we've had fights and stuff but
And he is kind of like a
Provocative but a lot of there's a few provocateur. I don't care about things provocative
I care if it's it's beyond that level as soon as it goes down a level
Okay
You might see if I was the focus wasn't on me. Yeah
Yeah, and so maybe it's like maybe just take a little take a like a little break. You know, maybe I need to take a break
You know, it's like
Or scale it down, you know
Yeah
That's yeah, so
You had Janet a pain support of his channel when all he does is try to create, okay
Okay
Yeah
If you go you can go to Sam and chat
He'll probably have you up on the panel and you can have all the discussions you want you can say anything you want
No, you can flip to him
How much he wants to talk and
The argument, I mean, that's his show, it's just really, I mean, I'm happy to have a show people clip and people like and there's content, but it's like, you know, I'm not making my show for clip, I'm making my show for me and my audience and then people clip it.
It's publicity, but he, you know, he's here all the time, he's here every day, not just for you, maybe the past couple times, he's here, he's been here almost every day, whoever's whoever's here.
There's Bita and Eldo and it's I know him for a long time probably since I started my panels almost so
So there's more of a history like so some people I will have more trust with right
Because I know them longer if so even if they do that kind of I just know they're not
You came to you want you I can't it came to instigate drama on my panel, okay, or he comes to okay
I know, but that's what I feel like you guys are doing.
I feel like you guys are doing, right?
So you can use it for his channel.
Yeah, I know, but I don't really mind being clipped,
I said, it's like, you know, sometimes he can,
sometimes the content can be more interesting
and then it benefits everybody, but the only reason he's,
here's not you, it is, yeah, it may be for drama,
but you know, he has a different kind of show.
Yeah
Yeah, I like I like what Dennis and saying so let's look at the chat
Hey, okay, so this is such a weird stream. Yeah
Sorry guys. It is I'm just trying to I want to really
Fix I want to fix this I can't be fixed, you know
Really it's like it's important to me
that not only everyone everyone walks away feeling okay, but
I do too. Okay. You're back. Oh, you're backstage. I'm sorry. Hold on backstage. Oh, he was one
Lady was talking about I'm alive someone. Oh
Hold on
Jam was oh, yeah, and so and Jan like some of the no jam is jam is okay. They've done the
Rusty rusty and you're perfectly fine and I understand you're a little bit, you know, you're
You know really a hardcore Trump and you know you have some interesting arguments, but
Your arguments really weren't to
Resonate with me
You're like, I know it's you're like, you know what you're doing is wrong, but you don't care
Hit somebody else does it. I mean it was just she doesn't I mean she at least she she was very honest like so
Yeah, I do have 25
2500 it's very honest
You know, I like kind of interesting, you know eccentric type people and it's fun, you know, but I need to
Just make sure everyone's
You know
Behaving themselves in the channel. It's too hard to please it. I just hope it's I'm dealing with adults
No, it's 21 over. I wish people would be able to
Nah, they can't act. They can't
They you have to you have to do it
every panel has to
You know do it would you have to figure out is what your boundaries are what you?
Principles you want and what you want the show to be about and then you have to enforce that unfortunately with an iron fist
Whatever that is now yeah, it could some people just want an open shit show
And then you don't have to really do anything but lay back and eat Cheetos
But if you want to foster constructive conversation you have to be very picky and very authoritarian
unfortunately
Yeah, and it's like and I had you know, I've had great drama. Okay. There's been great drama panels and a lot of
classic moments and
Interesting things like nothing that was really too harmful rather than name-calling, right?
And it's in the name calling as long as it's not the racial stuff. I really don't care about that, but
It doesn't seem like stuff to self-resolve. It seems like it's way other stuff other than this. How about like, you know, everyone? I encourage you
Especially if you do this kind of stuff just make your own channel and do it there
They don't go trashing other people's panels
People you know, they don't think he said he doesn't care if my channels
He doesn't care
And what what motivation does he have to follow the rules because he didn't care about you didn't care about following the TOS because it's
So I mean I have to so I have to step in so I don't know I really have to
and be able to trust them, right?
So yeah, so I know, now he's talking about salmon.
So you keep deflecting onto other people.
It's not about salmon right now.
We're trying to talk about you, okay?
What's the punishment?
Wow, I mean, I try to kick people up,
but then it's like, you know, I like people.
You don't really need to punish people.
The old thing is about fostering a conversation.
See, on my panel, say for example,
I'm way more strict.
So I don't even tell people or want people if they do something. I don't like
I get rid of them one way or the other so if they're on the panel, I'll put them backstage
And they'll just give me two minutes to cool off if they're in the chat. I'll time them out
Or if it's something that I that I think is more of a me thing and not a them thing
I'll literally remove the comment and not time them out at all and just let them keep going and
Just remove the comment that I don't want on my channel
You know, then if I pull you back up and you do the same thing again, then I might kick you off the backstage, not ban you, but just kick you, you know, you kind of get the point, right?
Then I might block you, then I might time you out for a day, you know?
Yeah, unfortunately unfortunately the people on my channel seem to be so first like very very and I know I've been persistent on a few channels
Like you know they kept month, but the mods kept blocking me
You know, so I've been you know people have been persisting in but I've been persistent trying to go another channels on a different account
So I understand why people do that here and stuff and but it's like it's impossible
If I can ban 30 of safety council be on another account just the name back there
I have, my heart hurts when I see, I'm like, oh my God.
And I feel sorry for some people.
I see this thing.
I'm like, oh my God, look at that.
Look at it.
He looks like he's, he needs a friend or something.
I try, then he comes on and says, oh, you know, he hates me.
So, yeah, and I'm not sure, Jamie,
like what's a video clip about you?
Who made the video clip about you, Jamie?
And make sure it's true.
Summer, believe me.
Thank you Summer.
I'm not sure what you're talking about, Jamie, but.
Yeah, I'm the only admin on the panel. So I have to run that
I rely on the mods for the chat. I think it's any better
just it's really
The more frustrated exhausted or upset I get the more he probably laughs. Okay. I know. Yeah, you try to tell me
Yeah
So I'm part of it too is people like a lot of people
to come here to use your channel like it's their own.
That's natural on YouTube, it happens on every channel.
Yeah, it's the way people are,
like they have their own agenda when they come here,
especially if they're a content creator.
And it's like, I had that problem too sometimes.
I had to remember.
Like where I'm at and everybody's entitled to run the panels that they want
And if I'm here and I can clearly see what it is that you don't like and I keep doing it at some point
Even if it's fair
It's not it's on me. Why am I somewhere where they don't want to talk about the things I want to talk about?
Right. I know I'm just pushing myself into his face where I'm not welcome. Yeah, and that's what and that's really JT
It's like maybe like JT maybe
Soon we can have like a one-on-one chat and we can talk and I'm not opposed to having you on the panel with me and stuff
but just joining all the panels and then
It seems when people join the panel then all this chaos starts happening and then then the word start flying and then the
Doxing and stuff and I have to end the stream and then it's like
There's no skin off your tits.
It's only one that hurts is me.
The only one that hurts is me.
Doesn't revolve, it doesn't dissolve anything.
So what's the point?
Like it's just gonna be, so, what's I'm saying?
So JT, I'll have a conversation with you one-on-one,
but it's not really, I think you need to
chill out on my channel because it's like I need to,
I don't know. You don't care. Not only do you not care if my channel gets taken down, do you care if
all my audience leaves and it's you know, it's purely people you brought in to troll me and
He claims he cares
that he just
didn't express himself fully
Yeah, he doesn't care. He said would you care? He's like well, he's like what doesn't affect me. It wouldn't affect me
That's what he said. Well, that's something
It's not in my control. Yeah, and it wouldn't be because of me like how did you know it wouldn't be because of you?
Like that one guy was like we use this other guy's picture the guy was about to strike my channel for privacy because he he
He shows picture and he's like, oh, I didn't do I can't figure out every little thing
I can't too much stuff to verify
So I gave you ever this song called better man. I can't hear you buddy, but my project like
Good morning, guys. It's 926 927 actually in the morning top of the morning to you guys
Oh
In the morning the sun still out is 927. This is nine o'clock in the morning
Right the sun's not out yet here
It's ugly
So I'm about here. Oh, it actually is the morning it takes 27 here
It's like he I'm so fucking drunk. I thought it was nine o'clock at night and I was going to pull a joke
Like you ever wake up and it was still the stomach was out and you thought it was morning time
But it was nighttime and you're like, oh, it's eight in the morning, but it's eight at night
I know I talk a lot. Sorry psyche. No, no, why do you come here so much?
But you're very missed
I'm just uh, you know, it's a
comforting it's a comforting thing because
Let's just
Um, I'm not saying you're banned at reading cars, but when Paige read my cards, she was exactly right
Yeah, the page has a challenge everyone go to pages down to we there's many
Well good, thank you page if you're out there page. Thank you very much sweetheart. Thank you sweetheart. Bye Joe
Anyway, yes
page is a great reader but um Jesus the only at the out the divinity uh do not
just create i know and it's crazy yeah uh oh oh joe's mad oh my gosh joe's mad
oh he's mad why is he so mad oh i got that redheaded temper out
yeah so that's what i meant too
Hey, Joe, I bet beat is a better terrier than me too, right? I bet beat is right
Yeah
Trump cars major arcana number one magician, right?
You know, I thought it was 6 30 p.m. Yeah
Yeah, guys during the swamp, right? How about they have it these people that cause nothing nothing but problems for me
Have a
To this I get understand maybe I was being weak
But you know what was weak that I kept letting him back on that I let them come in the first that was that so maybe I was weak
You're right. I was weak because
Kept forgiving you. I could give you chances. I kept wanting to like, you know, bring you on. I kept wanting to put Alex to
Yeah, that's pretty weak
Maybe I'll maybe I'll be a little bit stronger
Just run the panel like I want you. Okay. I can't even see that comment
What was the comment hold on something about you being weak
Oh, yeah, that was yes look last night
That's what he typed in the chat and God he typed it to and then tonight got someone said I forgot who it was
It said someone said it you gotta like hey, how will we clap sakes channel or tonight or something?
I bet you could or something they're talking about that right right in front of me like a like
Don't see it or it's funny or something. I don't know then he's like, oh, yeah, they were saying it
But it was a joke. It's not funny to me
It's like, is it funny to like threaten someone's livelihood?
I don't know, is that funny?
Hey, Saiki, thanks for letting me catch up
with the rest of you and gotten to talk for a while.
Good, I'm glad, I'm glad you guys got to talk.
I love bringing people back together
or having a place where people can talk, you know.
A.T., please, you're welcome in the chat.
Like, you can type in the chat,
you can express yourself there.
I can't.
What what do you what do you want? What do you want from me? What do you want like? Oh, just let you come on
Whenever you want and say whatever you want
Try to let people everyone say what they want to you within the guidelines
Okay, I've already been through so I've already been through some of this shit. It's not fun. It was like one of the worst
My channel got taken down or taken down for a little bit the first time. No one no one really cared
I mean a few people were there I care and people did follow me to my other channel, you know, but
You just I see no one really that my channel goes down today. No one really it was just
Remember that I remember how weird a show is remember how it was just be like
It's kind of they'll just kind of laugh at my failure. Oh, Joe. I don't like the angry face. You're making me
I don't like it make me come back later. I
Let you say you said what you wanted to say
Okay
Then the guy except when you look at doormat and you're a good you give him another chance
But that's that's my I think that's my stupidity. That's my weakness is like I want
To get everyone a chance
Yeah, I'm not given I'm not given second chances. I'm not ever good. I'm not given second chances
But if I fuck up in a chat just ban, that's it. There's nothing it's like, okay
What do you what are you saying loser who you're talking to?
All right, because I want to read out the what I wrote I say you're such a good guy, right that um you gave people so many chances and
Then you give them another chance and they usually like a doorman do it again
And then you give them another chance and they just keep on doing and they names like how many chances like you got to give you
to be on this panel
I don't know
Definitely, maybe it's not it's not their fault. You know, they're all they there's requesting to come on panel
It's my fault for keep letting him back up
My fault ultimately your responsibility. I wouldn't say it's your fault. No, he's a good guy. He's a good guy
He gives people chance. Yeah, look they take advantage of him
Right and and here's the thing he can be happy with that. I don't know if he is or he isn't I haven't been around long enough
But he could be happy with just giving people chances over and over again
Well, it's because I
Guys finish last I never
But I've never given a
I've never given I've never given a second chance and so I know how it feels not to be given a second chance
So I'll give second I'll give chances. I'll I'll be forgiving. I do think people can like
Maybe slowly, but I think they can
these
These come around to like the non-harmful part, but
I
Just it Joe, it's not the time I mean come on read the room
So that's okay. Anyway
I'm talking to the backstage. Yeah, I imagine he did and that's why he came up just to talk shit
Yeah, well, what's that about what you responding to?
You the the guy backstage. Oh, yeah, he's so drunk. He has no idea what's been going on for the last two hours or
There's trouble of put there's drama in the air there's blood in the water
So he's come up to fucking stir it several times. He's he's said f a g g o t n i g g e r
And I'm going to kill somebody and I'm gonna
Yeah, right
I am Joe I'm finally
You was in the backstage with me just now you is still in the middle, you know, you must have heard a little bit of something
Oh, yeah, so easy what was easy what happened with Sam and when my my show ended that one I ended with him
What happened backstage?
I was ripping him right he riffed a little bit saying he's gonna do this to them
He's gonna dox them he's gonna catch them, you know like he's gonna he's gonna he's gonna expose them basically
You're saying and then talk about who they were sleeping with
Yeah, it's okay. Yeah, but wait, but what Dennis and said was like he was kind of celebrating that
My stream got taken down. Like it was like
He chaired I got the recording you want to hear it? Okay
All right
Yeah, if it includes the the live like before you ended it as you ended it
Then yeah, the first couple of seconds you'll hear him kind of celebratory
okay, oh
It was almost braggadocious like like
He had a goal and he achieved
We can't hear that shit bro
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
Yeah, we just caught back up or you hit me on to Instagram. I sent the link in the back earlier
I don't know if you caught it. I'll send it right now if you get it
It's just like it's just like if I if I if I was sitting here in tears like pleading
He was if people would just laugh. He would
Yeah
So it's not there's no
It's like even like, you know, they're when I say they're you know, they're cordials that you was nice, you know, God's cordial
DT is cordial
But it's like they're not
Nice, it's not it's not like kind. It's like it's like
cordial for so it's like I think it's you beneficial purposes
Yeah, yeah, it's like a little bit
I don't know what they call it glazing maybe glazing. I bet it's not it's not really
Yeah, that's what that's what's called now glazing. It's not that it's I mean, it's not being that nice
because glazing is like, you know pouring on thick, but it's like
Just being polite, but it's like I
Don't think they're they're not but I know they're not polite. I think it's just like cuz it's like, you know, I
Don't know he's awesome
No, I'm just hit it chill man. Don't be so jelly about psyche everybody
Yeah
I mean
dope
That's just be it like I said, I'll have I can have people I can have people on a one-on-one basis
I can't have when some of these drama things even though it's entertaining for the audience
It doesn't accomplish anything. It just gets to show show
Okay
Billy slick
Yeah
I see I just need to see this is I need to be talk about I I'm
The things that said about me are worse than anybody in the chat. So
I don't know why he's complaining.
The chat talks worse than me than anybody else.
I'm going to retire.
There's a couple of people.
The chat goes hard.
Ever since I've been here for a few months.
The chat is wild, yeah, it's not a lot, but whose chat is not, all right?
Let's get that straight first.
Whose chat is not wild and insane?
What platform is mine wild and insane?
In the chat?
In the chat, people always go crazy.
It's like, no, not on my chat, they don't.
No, no, no.
It's not been like this easy.
I mean, maybe it was on your show, but I've been in, I was Benny Blanco's mom and Emma's
And they had a lot of shit being talked, but it's nothing like there's nothing like this. It's like nothing to this capacity. All right. Yes
On my stream
We would have been talking about something else
Right because I won't even if panel members start talking about moderation or what I do would don't allow I put them backstage
If they start complaining about
that how I do things I put them backstage same thing in the chat if they complain about them
in the chat I time them out and if someone said any of that shit about anybody on my panel even
if I didn't like the person I would time them out because I'm trying to facilitate a conversation
I'm not trying to suffer fools or create a platform for bullies to like rub their dicks on
I understand, yeah, that's a great point.
And yeah, that's why I'm doing these,
I'm really trying to brainstorm with some intelligent people
about this, get some other perspectives that, you know,
and when I was like, you know, when beta and good times
and...
Crystal and Mr. Bigpipes, there was like five people
that just like fucking went off on me last night
for pretty much no reason, you know?
When they talked to me like that, I was like, you know,
it hurt and I was like, wow, this, I know,
now I know how it feels when this person talks
to other people and it's like, I didn't,
maybe didn't know exactly, I thought it was kind of like,
you know, there's an audience number is different
than it happened to you, what happens to you
And so it's really it's really eye-opening and I probably have not been the best so I like I said
Like because you know, it's a balance trying to get with like, you know trying to entertain the audience with drama
And sometimes the fights are entertaining, but yeah, yeah, you were crystal. Please you were on saying I you're on making all these accusations
Yeah crystal I you're on yesterday your yes remember you came on it was probably 24 hours ago or less and you said
Yes, you were crystal and you said I called you a crack or and you said I called you Kim
And you're making other accusations about me and then you said FDGOT twice, okay?
Or actually many more times than that many more times and she does not remember it's okay. It's okay crystal you were
First I think you got a better chance coming on panel sober and only sober because your junk state is out of line and
Well crystal we'll just have to agree to disagree that it's now been deleted because you did say at they GGOT twice
And so I can't really prove it, but you know, I know everyone saw you here
You came after beta and it was long. Yeah, you came on you said I'm not coming on panel anymore
They came on like 15 minutes later. Okay
It's like
You said to have come to the panel. I don't want to say, you know, I know I didn't say that
Yeah, I forgot me. I see those here. I'm gonna see to use get me
I'll play you my bad
Yeah, I'm a mother
And that's another thing there's drunkenness in everybody's using the drunkenness of the excuses. I don't remember I didn't do this
I was drunk. I'm sorry
How many times you gonna hear sorry?
You know I'm saying how many times can someone tell you sorry and do the same actions over and over and over
Yeah, yeah, he remembers loser the loser remembers. Thank you loser for back in me
I remember I remember that's why I'm saying what I say
How many times you're gonna get slapped them somebody's gonna come and do something to you say sorry and then go repeat it again?
Sorry repeat it again. I'm sorry
Well, I mean I cannot
Like because sometimes people are drunk and they say stupid shit like you know because I've done it
You know and I and I've said well, I was drinking. I don't remember that
I have to sometimes take people's word for it. There's not always the video through for whatever
So yeah, so I've said that before too but
But I'm honest
Sorry everybody. We haven't technical difficulties. You're psychies. Please don't wait momentarily psyche. You're still muted. You're muted. Thank you
And look, do you hear me? Okay. Yes. Yeah, my my headphones are dying. Okay. It's okay, Crystal
Don't don't don't worry about it. Don't worry about it
You're fine. Nothing happening yesterday. Okay. Hello came in and said, oh, yeah, yeah, remember loser
Yeah, so I mean, that's that that's that I'm gonna
I've learned a lesson lesson is, you know, don't bend over back. Don't don't swim across the ocean for someone that wouldn't jump across a puddle for you. That's the thing, right?
Or step in a puddle for you
Yeah, definitely. Yeah, jump across the boat step. Yeah, exactly. Whatever it is
They don't they don't they're not putting their foot near the puddle when i'm fucking halfway swimming through the ocean for them. Okay
I don't know. I'm not gonna
I'm not like, you know, I'm not jesus. I can't like, you know
Sacrifice myself for somebody else, right? I have to be selfish
Okay
So I'll run my panel like I want to I'll run my show like I want to have it so my show happens in my show
The consequences whatever they'll be will always be my consequences not anybody else's no matter even if it is somebody else that causes it
They'll probably have a have a beer open a glass of you do a toast laugh at how
They ruin, you know, ruin someone's channel. I don't know. I'm not gonna have that. I don't like that idea
so
I'll have to be tougher and yeah, and Joe, I don't even know what you came on talking about. I don't know it's like
It seems like
People can say whatever they want to me. I can't say what I can't say anything. Okay
So that's it. That's it memories memory. Okay, so I think I think that's
How I have to move forward because
No one's gonna stop
Alex was I can't stop one step. Oh
I was so I got guys sometimes I cringe like
You know probably views right about some things like yeah, why why why did I give Alex so many chances?
I mean, I never see Alice's face. I mean, maybe I don't really know what he looks like so I'm not in love with him
But why do I why did I even like him? I've done didn't he say he showed you face in the backstage
Yeah, I saw it for like half a second. I saw like
I saw him. I don't want to put the picture because you said don't put pictures no more. Okay. I got that picture. That's what it is
Okay. Yeah, so yeah
Nothing I didn't fall in love with him at first. I don't know why I don't know why but I I really will
Give females another chance too, but
Jackie you're not the only one that likes Alex there like everybody's still giving chances all around YouTube
Everywhere, so it's like don't don't don't feel bad. It's everybody. It's not just you is
I guess we all just fall for this shit, sometimes he's nice and then he goes wild, sometimes
he's wild, then he goes nice, that's Alex.
I don't want to say to keep on giving him, everyone, but it's like I'm always the easiest
person to hate.
It's just so easy, maybe it's good, don't be mad at everybody else, everyone just get
mad at me, everyone just get mad at me.
Just pretend like I'm the problem. Even if it's not true just pretend
They're gonna be if everyone else gets along and everyone hates me. I'll be fine with that if everyone else is getting along
Yeah
Yeah, like yeah, everyone like the Sunday stream. This is the this is a church
Good morning guys
My Jesus getting your soul
I mean, it's like and then I really like
Most of the time I'm on this panel
I'm just doing it. I'm doing it for fun. You have a card. Sure lots of boyfriend, but you don't know how to help him get over
His ex and I'm too dumb to leave. No, I don't say you're dumb. Okay. Can you have a card? I love my boyfriend
Okay, well get over his ex. I mean you I think if you with you he should be over his ex. I mean not over his ex
that's kind of a
I don't think it's your responsibility to help him get over his ex I have to do is you know be you he should
Not be thinking about his ex. I don't know
Situations like you will clean. Hold on
Number no, but I just pulled the card for her. So this is okay, so
Okay, you see, okay, so this seven of wands, okay, there's some kind of guard up
Okay
well
really
There's I mean, there's this guard should be up when it comes to if he's still obsessed with his ex. I don't know
He should be getting over his ex
In a loving relationship, I don't know why he's still
See seven ones
It's a seven of ones suggests you're you're facing tough competition
See you see if you saying he's still in love with his ex or can't get over his ex that's
Feelings for so that's competition, right?
If someone is trying to go between you and your goals, hold your ground. This isn't the time to let down your guard, keep your defenses up, and give it your all.
Yeah, I'd say tell him not to fucking... His ex doesn't exist anymore.
Don't let him talk about his ex. He's trying to make you jealous or something and watch out for that
Watch that watch that because it sounds like some kind of manipulation, too
He's
You're better than his ex
Yeah, yeah, but just you know
Don't don't let him talk about his ex or triangulate you if he's saying it's your responsibility to help him get over his ex
That's ridiculous
Okay, Miguel. Oh
You're trying to help them back together
well
Okay, you're trying to help. Oh, you're oh, he's your ex okay. We're trying to help them back together
kind of confusing question, but
What this says basically just beyond guard it's like I wouldn't get involved
Wait, I'm confused you said I love my boyfriend
Yeah, but I don't know how to help him get over his ex. Yeah, and I don't know what it's a dump to leave
But I want them to get back together
Yeah
Didn't it doesn't make sense, but I mean I'll just take the advice
I'm not exactly it doesn't matter really matter what the question was but it just says
There's some kind of competition or something and to be on your guard. Okay?
Okay, you're welcome. Okay. Thank you
Uh, I know it was maybe it was this
Okay, so
She's saying that she tried to fix their relationship first
They got together
Okay
Okay, well you got the 10 of cups 10 of cups. This is like the the ultimate happiness card, you know, there's a lot of
You know 10 is emotions, right?
And so this is like the the 10 things like the very strong but they're the happiest
It's the most probably most positive cups card
This is what everyone's looking for the 10 of cups is like the happily ever after this is like the the
The home life is good. Everything is good. Okay
10 of Cubs says 10 of Cubs represents
our
happiness while you're home within your home family and
a close
knit circle
You're feeling supported
Understood and appreciated lucky you let your loved ones know how much
You value and appreciate them. Okay, so
Thank you. I understand. I do appreciate my family. They've been helping me a lot.
Yep, and if you, you know, if Gamma is helping you, that is definitely a big blessing. And so, yeah,
there you go. Right, loser? In the cat chat, yep. So, that's a nice card. I like that pretty easy.
Thank you. I'm thinking about, like, what it means, where it lands. So, yeah, they've been helping me.
Yeah. Welcome. So, okay. Yeah. So it's been a little bit, a bit crazy. Wow. It gets kind
of a thing that bothered me most is the, the carpet mini. Yeah. And so if that resonates
So I think something's going on beyond like the earthly realm with some of the stuff that's going on
There's like I think there's spiritual stuff going on with this. That's why I think
Prayers aren't for right now. Also, I just it feels like there's something else. There's some there's more
To do with stuff. We can't see them. We can't in this issue and in the situation something off with the energy of everything
Right, like yeah, I've been feeling way too about stuff, but especially for people that are like, you know
Spread and then people like for all people to turn on the same time kind of thing. It's like
it's kind of
How weird I know I don't I don't know but did anyone see a lecture if she went to betas
I think she did go to betas tonight, and I don't know how it went, but
Just beat it doesn't sound like herself
I don't know like I don't know what I can do about it. I can't you will have to fix it you're gonna find the way to
That's why she's actually be friends and not like let these other people show you apart
It's so hard because it's like, I don't she's like I
Try to give space and like I hear all this like, you know, she's mad. I'll just like give her some space
Oh, you don't call and check on me and then I
Would then she probably be just yelling at me. It's like I can't win sometimes. Oh
God true in life. Sometimes there's like sometimes there's like your damn if you do your damn if you don't
Something's up literally for life. Okay. Yeah, definitely sounds like a marriage
I'm damned if I do I'm damned if I don't cuz trust me that's it
Yeah, I lose it. That's what I'm trying to do like that's why I
like don't try to like, you know people panel alone and
See she's been coming over here. Just attacking me right your friend on yourself be
shit on yeah
It's like
It's more important for me to feel a friendship than to, you know, to be offended about anything.
She said, I'm not mad. I'm just like, the loser, I do that to my boy.
Like, I don't even talk to him. I haven't talked to him in like, not much, but anybody can start
talking about him. I'm like, yo, don't talk about my man like that. Like, you know what I'm saying?
But still, like, my mind, even though we might not talk no more or whatever, but I still ain't
going to let nobody bash your name.
Yeah, and I certainly don't and I don't want to say anything like
I'm not I never tried to attack her and I'm a great person. It's like I just I'm worried
Everybody else they kind of bug me ever except a joker. I like joker too. I know I think he was just trolling but everybody else they were just like
I don't know if it was
We go get mad psyche if you just drop the rule like
Don't talk about my friend be the you talk about I'll kick you off. I'll care who you are
Don't talk about if you guys are nice and say, okay, but you talk about I don't want to hear that. Yeah, don't talk about be there
It's hard because it's not that I don't want you talking about her here. That's my friend. Don't talk bad about her
Like when one of the first times I got clip was been like raging demon came on one night and said he's quitting YouTube and was crying and
She was on and so but
When he came on like she eventually she says here. She's like she's like just put me out alone with him one-on-one
You know it's that you know she didn't say kick him off the panel
She's like put on one-on-one and so everyone else went off the panel and so then there was like all this all this
drama
Yeah
My way
It gotta go both ways to if somebody's talking bad about you she got to defend you and somebody you talking bad about her
Somebody's talking about about her on your page. You got to defend her like it goes away too. Yeah
Yeah, but okay, but I'm saying you saying with the raging demons stuff. Yeah
She said put me on one on one with them like and so I went backstage you had one on one big conversation
It was a long conversation. He calls a bunch of names that horrible things. She's she sounded like she was sitting her ground
She said she was laughing when he said this stuff then she's like you let him call me this and that
Well, it's like, you asked me to put one-on-one, and so, you know, if she would say, and she said,
she told me, drop people before. And if they're, you know, and I would always do it. But then,
like, the other night, she was like, you know, LD was on, and he was just being polite in the chat.
Like, tonight, he was,
He just let me I didn't like tonight, but yeah, so he was be nice in the check
He wasn't doing anything. She's like kick him off the panel and I was like well
He's fine with why and she's a kick him off the panel
I'm counting ten and and she counted down from ten to one and I
just like I
Was like I never tell her
Bring this person up on panel or don't bring this person up in panel. Why why could she tell it to me?
It's like
That's why that's why I was like well
I just not gonna like be like a little bitch and like she you know do whatever you just just could you tell me and the
Kids not doing anything, but if he was or if anyone was I would have kicked him off if she asked, you know, but sometimes
you know she's into the
To the drama and fighting sometimes too and so it's like I
How do I know what's an offender or not? She's actually been called many worse things by other people, you know
DJ lecture might have said the B word or something like that and she was yelling a lecture for that
Oh, you call me that and lecture they remember and I don't think she I don't know
Maybe I don't know if she's it or not. She said she wasn't directing it. I don't know
But it seems like well, she just called her bitch once it's like, you know
If you're friends sometimes you can call your friend a bitch
No, she certainly called me a bitch pussy and other stuff. Maybe okay. She didn't say f a g g o t
I just thought she had typed that because it said f and then the rest of the word was like a bunch of
Okay, so who's this guy? So this is a Henry saw Zika's. Hold on. Hold on a second Henry
You know this guy easy
Hello
Henry Harry hi, how are you? Yeah
What you been here before? How are you today?
Yeah
You're good. What's going on with this fucking fragger on your panel
He's a fragger, you know, you know
Are you guys a bicycle? Yeah
Okay, what's uh, what's the F word guys? What can we not say? No, no F a g g o t
No n i g g e r why why why what's wrong with that word?
Because it's against the to s and I'm a monetized channel, so I'd appreciate if you just yeah, but it's like a fun work, you know
Yeah, it's a word. It's it's not but it's not fun for my show when it's a monetized show and I can get you know
Strikes for you know hate speech and stuff like that. Really? Yeah, no way. Are you making shit up right now?
No, I'm not making shit up. You are
No, oh
So who's this guy ease on your channel?
You don't know easy. I thought you know, you know me. You know me. He's just playing stupid right now a psyche. He's really playing
You don't know him
Okay, well, no, no, okay, so there's a okay, so Harry
I know that you're making accusations with a lot of the show. Okay. No, no, no, that's that's that's that's true facts
Okay, okay. Oh, you did. Okay. Well, I've met that. I've met today. Okay. It's all over YouTube. I've met today, too
Okay, I've got no problem with that
So he should be up. So why would you remove me?
I don't know
Do what the fuck he wants about it. Why are you why are you protecting why you protect knees that you know?
Is it some kind of protection for him
No, no, no, no, I don't know the I don't know the details of this case
Okay, I beat that case. I beat that case. I beat that case. Okay. Yeah, that case with the lady. I beat it
You beat her in the case
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, she's she's um deck me three times and then I told you touch me again
I'm gonna defend myself. She spit in my face and then went right in my mouth
You see the reaction you gonna get
Well, you know, maybe if you
No, we're straight you enjoy that she was across the sheet working. You said right he was across the sheet from that incident
Why did he come outside to be super bad and do something?
No, I didn't you're lucky if I would have came outside
I wouldn't have been sad but you said you was working across the street that day, but you
Said I worked in the best. I'm up. I'm a loud mother. I'm a loud mother screaming. I'm heard you heard
Yeah, I said I worked in that area not across the street. They could
Relax
You said across the street what happened to me
No, I said I work drama. You don't want to build the drama you bring you don't like drama
We just having a perfect conversation. You come with this guy. He's directing everything at me
Yeah, dude because it is what it is, you know what I'm saying
Nothing wrong what it is. Let me guess what you did. You mad your other panel got taken down
What happened with that shit, what'd you do, bro?
I don't know what happened, but you mad your other panel got taken down
So you finally caught the ball. I'm saying what you do what you do
You finally caught the balls to come back here and harass me
As you know, this is my this is where I'm at now. This is where he's even like so you're not going
But why why what's going on with this?
So you're not at you're not at money for money money for 20
You know harassing Miguel now you over here you and your your little girl's spying and ready to report me in any
Way possible you you what you you still got that pinching going on huh?
Let's get that pinch if it get ease your future. Come on. Let's get that pension, huh?
No, it's a petition. There's another thing I want to talk about something you get when you work like you just don't allow
It's just a don't allow something you get when you work when you have a job
You know, yeah
Petition is something you start
Petition there you go petition. I said, yeah, it don't matter. I know what I was talking about though. No, dude
I'm correcting you. I ain't making fun of it. All right. It's all right. It's all right. That's perfect
I can't I can't right now something. That's all ready
Oh, you got a thousand signatures. Let me ask you that you got a thousand signatures already. You working on it
That's why you can find how many we need
You need a thousand. I'll just get fucking pick with the fucking put all his fucking signatures
How many fucking accounts does that retard have? Oh, yeah, you need you need government signatures
But they can look at what? Yeah, you need they names and and maybe sometimes they addresses
So I don't know if it's gonna work out for you Papa. Oh
Well, I'll just make up everything dude. Oh
Go ahead do that. I'll love it for the report
Is that you would have done that anyway, dude, you would have done that anyway, even if they were legit
Right
You're more calm tonight
You're more calm. I'll give you that one. You're more you're more civil right now, but I always am you guys freak out
What you talking about bro? I'm always like this you guys start screaming and yelling
Like you're panicking like a dog is a late like a fucking mad dog is coming down the block and you're jumping on cars to get away from it
You know what I'm saying? It's not my fault. I'm just walking walking down the block. What are you doing up on a car?
Well, you acting all stupid
your
When a dog walk ass
Hey, I mean
Yeah, I mean
Are you hearing me?
Do I scare you bro
No way brother. No way. No, I'm just not gonna react to what you want me to do spaz out go crazy
I'm just saying am I scary bro. I'm gonna crash out for you
Look, I know you I knew y'all gonna come over here cuz just did right now. Please crash out man
Your crush your sheet is off so you're gonna come here everybody's gonna come here
Yeah
It been proven already. You're the first one now. I would came here. I would have came here regardless
Just to fuck with you, man
You're like a target. Oh
Yeah
Don't worry. Did you hit the like on your way in at least?
Now, I don't really like any videos dude. I'm not like that. You know, I'm not I'm not a nice person, bro
You're a nice guy compared to me you're nice, you know what I'm saying, but
Yeah, you just try to be charming you try to come around
Try to change people's a you know idea of you
but, uh, yeah, bro.
I mean,
it's not gonna change my idea.
Did I ever deny anything?
Did you hear me ever deny anything?
Nah, but I'm just saying that, you know,
the type of guy you are is the type.
No matter what path I'm on,
no matter what app I'm using,
wherever I'm at in the street,
next to the cops,
Fuckin a bitch no matter what I'm doing
Let me answer your question. Would you hit a kid? I'm a be me. We have would you hit a kid?
Why would you I'm asking you? I'm just asking you would you say you hit a kid?
I remember you say if it wasn't you ask a stupid-ass question if the kid now you're fucking talking stupid, right?
I'm just asking you bro. Would you hit a kid?
question
Well, would you hit a 16-year-old would you hit a 16-year-old kid?
If a 16-year-old kid was hitting you would you hit him? I'm a grown-ass man. Go get your phone
Yeah, but some 16-year-olds are big too
All right, I'm 14 to 15 year old would you would you knock out a 14 to 15 year old kid?
Answer the question you you still but if they were hitting you would you hit them?
So can you Harry you Harry? Why you don't let your wife on panel?
Why she had why you have to have a conversation on online listen, man
Men like me control women, bro. Not because we want to but because they want they want to be controlled
And you that type of person so you do yeah, they write a list and tell me
I want you to say these things to me and forget. Yeah, bro. What do you think bro? You beat your wife?
With my dick on the inside beat the fuck out of her
You sure you're not being largely
But I beat the I beat her up beat the bitch up
Beat the bitch up all day long
What I said though you forgot to ask me to get online some shit like that
You demanded her. Oh, you you didn't ask me to be on line
Right, I said you fucking ask like what I was stupid. I thought you was talking to me
That's your wife like your wife. What are you doing? Like, you know, what are you doing?
Like, what do you think you are this other fucking?
Bitch running around or whoever fucking runs around for you. Yeah, but he's crazy, bro
Now with me now with me, bro. Yeah
You listen, bro, you beat women with your hands
I beat him with my dick and then they just the most submissive that way the way you do it, brother
Just I was saying that I was saying that the other time you bite me right now
But I saw me in your bitch on my cock from the back and he was tight clap clap clap clap clap
Yeah, that's a new song I'm having a relaxed morning. I'm having a relaxed morning
Is that your new song? How's your morning? How's your morning going?
Good man. I'm taking a shit at the moment right now talking to you. You're
You're shitting your heart out get it
Yeah, bro. Oh you talking so shitty. What about your morning? What'd you do you beat up any women today?
Any women piss you off at a point where you got a beat on them
Hear that nice cup of coffee right there
Yeah
I like to take a shit and drink my coffee at the same time
I got a joint having a good conversation with Psyche
Mr. Joe runs out there after real quick, y'all
Yeah, I had a nice conversation with Mr. X and Psyche this morning
You didn't even come up here and ask the host how he's doing you just came straight towards attacking each
But what happened with McQuaid, bro? You guys broke up?
Don't worry about what happened with McQuaid
I'm just
Brooklyn to Queens and do what you do go visit him
Take it by me and him. I'm gonna read a lot across from me. I don't have a problem with McQuaire
I don't have a problem with McQuaire. Why would he have a problem with me? Go buy him a bean year
Go buy him a beer. Go have fun. Go choose. I don't drink dude. You know, I don't drink
But if he wants to drink it's fine. It doesn't matter. I said go buy him a beer. How about that?
Go buy him a round of cocaine and y'all can split it
Go fuck with it. I don't I don't say
Would you would you fight would you like fight a woman boxer like
You know like that bitch that was running around saying she was gonna knock out all the men like to suck my dick
I'm just saying would you fight like a woman boxer all you're doing right now you suck
I ain't one no
my dick just relax Harry
Clarisse Clarisse something right
When you go come back man, I want to have a conversation. I can't bet you that bitch will beat you up
I bet you that bitch will beat you up, bro. Let me have a conversation. Thank you. Let's see. We have a conversation
Okay, yeah, thank you. No, thank you. You got you got what you want. Absolutely, man
I have having you wanted to get off. So he's be all right. Oh shit
Yeah, I mean
Everything I mean, it was just here
He's a mumble. I'm telling you it's I don't it will never end
Me it would never end but I'll get over it like these people who try to make me miserable is not gonna make me miserable guy
No matter what you do, no matter what you say, I am who I am and I will admit to everything I did
I'm not I'm different
Yeah
But yeah, I don't know there's a lot of so I didn't know anything about
The accuracy of any of this stuff, so I don't know glad you got to talk to a book
Yeah, I thought you were gonna come up here one day. It's starting going crazy. I didn't want to put the bike picture
I was thinking about it like I said, no bitch it's fuck
Yeah, thank you someplace else. I'll just start having fun
Yeah
Now but he's an interesting conversation is if you can have a right conversation with him
You know I'm saying but it's just sometimes he drifts sometimes he likes to nag and poke at people and but you know
He's a good conversationist. I can't give it. I can't doubt that I'm not gonna doubt that he's a good conversation
You got out if he got stick to a conversation instead of being a I thought he's gonna bring up the um the Greeks
But he didn't
I'm not worried about it
Okay, yeah, but he's still back stage. Do you want to talk to me again?
If you can have a good decent conversation. Yeah, I don't mind is Japan or you could you could do what you want?
Okay, oh
I remembered her name bro Clarissa Shields Clarissa Shields, bro
You know that woman
Easy is this dog?
She's a female boxer, right?
Yeah, bro. She was calling out all the fucking men. She's like I beat all the men up. You know me
Is that the is that the trans UFC lady you talk about nah, bro. That's like a woman like a woman woman
Clarissa Shields
She was calling out all the men and then something happened. I think some guy knocked it out. I
Think she fought yeah, I think yeah. Yeah. It was like all women women. Oh, I think I might be right
Yeah, I think I think she did have a fight in the UFC
One right, I don't know you might be right or some fucking MMA organization
She's not
Neither I need to refer my cup. I'll be right back
He's calling her a trans she's no trans. She's a pure woman. She's not a fucking
And that's somebody else somebody else that's another let me talk about someone else you're talking about that dude
That was like a military guy get to know psyche don't like you know
Let's get to get to know psyche since it's like your second time up here. You never really got you guys man
I see you guys fucking Speedos and shit ankles behind it is I'm very familiar with you guys
Well, I mean it's a
Right, right, right exactly
Or the Olympics, you know. Yeah, yeah
The Prince will make me in contest
Right. Yeah
So what was the conversation
What were you guys talking about and missed everything?
Well, there's just been a lot of you know people coming on
making it like you know wanting to
Huh, I don't know. I'm just trying to protect my chat and people are coming in. I don't know. Everyone's everyone's mad. Yeah, I will everyone's
kind of like
Got a lot of stuff going on here and a lot of drama. I'm just trying to help sort through it so we can
I've been formed over a hundred times, you know, I mean, I've never I've never why why
Do I think yet? Well, I know I know some of them. I know some of them. I know like, you know, for example
It's a blackout Andy was here today with doing it
Tony the conductor does it and then many other people I love maybe some random people, but yeah a lot a lot of people
As to something. Oh
What's the question? I
I'm saying do you think that the jealous or or or something went wrong because you're not giving him no ass
Well, it's been happening since my I started doing open panels probably since almost the first day
I started doing open panels and I do a lot of open panels. I have a lot of
Trolling communities here. I there's a lot of people that have stuff. They don't like or people. They don't like on the show
That I have on and so I mean there's a lot of different reasons that can happen
Some people just do it just to fuck with you some people
Sit there and try to do it all the time. I don't know
Been on for a lot of hours and so it's happened a lot
It's happened a lot, but it's probably been attempted more than I it's actually happened and I'm always joined smash. Sorry. Sorry psyche
I just went to the chat
Hi smash
Yeah, I had a couple conversations when he seems like a cool guy. I met him at Summers, I believe I've seen him on other platforms
but I met him on something oh
cool, yeah, I love summer and
Yeah, it's just it. So you have a channel. Um, do you have a channel?
Let's see Harry. Harry. I'm sorry, Harry
You got a bike channel, that's how that's how far this picture and stuff like that. He does all bike runs
Oh, he's saying he good. Well, let him tell his story
Okay
Harry
Yeah, where's it's wondering about you know, I know you have like, you know
$10,000 rims on your bike and you really I really did. I don't know what kind of bike you have you're really into bikes, right?
Yeah
Don't the tracks
Okay, I got up to the like from 2006 to 2015 models
Nice the top end ones, but I skipped a few years. They make them every three years
Every three years don't make the new model
Hmm. I just got I just got my a bike my first my first
transportation in a long time electric bike and
It's pretty pretty cool. It's
So how long you said you haven't had a bike for before that? Oh, oh, I had what I had a I mean
I had a car up to like 2017 2018 and then since then I haven't had anything I'm barely I once I
I wrote around a scooter for a little while, but you know, I really I've been walking for the past several years though
It's cool to have like everybody goes like 26 27 miles an hour now
Hey smash and so yeah, I love I love bikes
Nice flat. I live in a nice flat area. I'm gonna need a car and so it's a cool e-bike though. I
Love the e-bike
This guy sounds like an authentic New Yorker. Yeah, you're from your New York. So you're here. I've been I've been degrees actually here
Have you been degrees?
Yeah, when I was younger I went there a few times, but I need to revisit now
Yeah, it's been it's been a few years
I went when I was like 14, uh, homestay, I went to Athens and I, uh, I stayed with the family in like a, a little village.
So what's the farthest you wrote, Harry? You wrote across state, across country?
I'm not really too much of a, uh...
Don't I don't go distance. I'm more of a short more intense effort kind of rider
You know, I don't really do distance, but I was gonna do Florida a few years ago. Go from New York all the way down to Florida
I was gonna do that. You should do it this year. You can come visit me. I
Know you're not down there stupid. You're fucking somewhere around here. Stop fucking capping, bro
You know who Lisa stop caring about here. You know who Lisa Jordana is
Who the Jordana's?
Lisa Jordana, she's in Florida
Sounds familiar
She had the domestic incident last year in the car with a boyfriend on stream
She's really pretty
She's in Boca Del Rey
and
Whatever happened with that situation where she hit the boyfriend, right? Yeah, she got arrested and
She pled guilty. I think she spent a day in jail since you got a year probation and
That was it and she's just finished the probation and so she's fine now
But yeah Amanda Harry's gonna be your tour guide when you go
How are you got echo?
Let me see if I can fix it, let me see if I can fix it, hold on.
Hello? Is that better? That's better.
A little bit better.
No one will recognize her, let me see.
Okay.
Hey Amanda, good night Amanda, thank you for being here.
Oh, good night Amanda.
How are you going to be a slow guy to your grease adventures?
Is it night already? What do you mean? Good night?
The fuck's going on where is she? Oh that shit rolled straight under there
Someone's yelling
Outside. Oh, yeah, I'm doing I'll be fine a minute. Thank you. It's just you know, I feel like I'm working
I think I feel like things are working. It's a lot better than it was yesterday. So it's already better
The people are tea. Oh, yeah, it's like, I guess her TPP close shut down today. I don't know
Damn it. Everyone else stop only I am allowed to blame her for okay
So say it's the leader of the Luminati snoop. Oh gosh. Oh, no, I've been up all night. I've been
For a few hours, yeah, let's see
What was Amanda
Amanda is on the chat, but she was up here earlier. Good night Amanda. Good night loser
All right, anybody's going to bed see if you close down hours and hours ago. Yeah, I mean, I've been up for hours an hour
So it's very 17 minutes in this tree
Yeah
interesting day
This was better than the day before but
Still hope everything
Yeah, I'll get okay, but I will I'll fix all all fix it. I'll fix it
Harry, um, can you go to all more or the audio switch it from?
The fall to speaker and it'll fix the audio
It's already there and everything is on
I don't think it's me
No, it definitely was
Yeah, I know it's better now. Thank you so much
Okay, hey, Brian
Was I heard the noise
Did you hear me? Yeah, what'd you say?
You said you had an electric bike. Yeah, I just got an electric bike. It's it's a
It was used so I got like, you know a pretty good deal and
That's my first bike in a long time. It works really well. It goes like 25 miles an hour
What's the what's the what the battery life like the distance it can give you
Mm-hmm. I'm not sure but since I've had it the batteries never died
It's like I always just keep charging it seems to last a long time
I need to like ride long enough but I only go on short little neighborhood trips
I need to be on it long enough for it to to drain but it looks like it lasts a long time. It's a
It's a great bike
Yeah, it's like a $2,000 bike, but I got it for like 200 bucks. I just paid it off
Yeah
And one it went for a while. Yeah, so we'll probably give you around
Like 30 to 50 mile distance on one charge
Wow, yeah, I want to I'd love to like ride my bike to Venice one day because I'm down the down the
the beach from Venice
too far too far to walk but I could take a bike there and
That'd be cool to stream there. I live in like LA so
Beautiful Southern California. Yeah, California is the best fucking state in America
They got the best fucking weather, you know, it's always dry heat out there, you know
So you don't have the humidity that Florida has, you know, yeah
California is cool and it's expensive and the people aren't very nice, they're not the
friendliest.
They've been to other places and they're a lot friendlier people than they are in California.
There are the most beautiful people here too though because the most beautiful people from
all around the world come here to go to Hollywood and a lot of them work as waitresses and waiters.
Hold on. So Brian, where's that? Where are you 85 degrees 75% humidity? That's hot. It's getting warm here already. I'm fucking sweating
Yeah, it's disgusting over here in New York
Disgusting it's raining. It's fucking humid. It's the worst like a hundred degrees. It's disgusting. Oh, no
Yeah
Are you friends with Alex your friends with Alex?
No, none of us are friends
Okay
None of us are friends whose friends whose friends well, I thought I was fucking talking shit to everybody, you know
I thought I was friends with Alex. I did but yeah
Yeah, but uh, yeah, everybody thinks they're friends with Alex
Alex is not friends with the set with himself that fucking guy's got like 300 personalities
It depends which is gonna be you know, it depends how much coke he does
You know, you know, if he does like, you know, two lines, he'll be this guy if he does three, he'll be that guy
four, he'll be this person. So
depends
Well, you Alex, you know, you're fucking listening you're fucking McQuaid
I mean I banned them because he like he like it started attacking me and like in the chat and then
Why just out of nowhere?
This out of nowhere. Yeah, but why do you let him get to you?
Well, because it got me and it's like no he said they should be for like if it was like
Yeah, you know and he's been mad at me before we had fights
But this time it was like so I was like I'm provoked and he just started attacking me and saying really bad things about me and
Insinuations and asking like this like trying to embarrass me and I mean you're just really out of line
But I did let him on again last night
Just because I was I was off stage and like there's a couple people on panel
I let him on he was like he was drunk, and he was like
Oh, he does set me here and then
Then he left, so I don't know he's like hanging out with Bita from now on. I think I think
They've teamed up against me now. I think Bita was the one that
Bita is mad because Alex
Add Alex on my show. She's so mad about that and then she has him on her show tonight. What's the fuck?
Yeah, it's just words man, you know, I don't think anybody should allow it to get to you
You know don't allow that shit to get to you
No, I mean, I just I just don't like to be talked like that on my show by Alex who I've been yeah, but you know
I mean, it's it's like let's just it's just I don't know it
It's like there like there like I like Alex and I bet he was like a little heart and
He would break the rules and he wouldn't follow them no matter what and I had to keep telling him
And I also put myself on the line because people were like leaving the show getting mad the women were getting offended
I was like I told him. Hey, he's a good guy. He's actually a good guy
and then they'd be like no, I don't like him and
People would leave and I would just keep standing up for him and then he just like turned on me
Yeah, he was on her stream already. Yes, he was
Yeah, but he's done that to everybody
Yeah
I've seen him do it. I've seen him do it, but not as bad as he did it to me
I mean, I've heard of you pretty rude. That's what I'm thinking. I was like, well, he is pretty rude
I didn't I didn't see how mean he was until he did it to me
Then I'm like, wow, he's really mean and it's like so I know how it feels and so I'm
definitely going to be stepping in when people start attacking people on the panel from no one
Yeah, he goes everywhere. He does that he befriends everybody and then all of a sudden he attacks them, you know
It's hard to deal with those personnel. It's hard to deal with those personalities because it's like
Yeah, that guy's a bipolar for sure. You know, maybe a bipolar bear
That's how fucking biggest bipolar is in this
You know
The character I always thought he was just I thought he was just mainly a character and so
But yeah, so that's why you know if you're gonna have
He have thick skin and I
Have I have thick skin, but there's a point when on my show to have him talk to me like that
Like yeah, but it's the internet and the more you take the more you could take the more
I think people will have respect for you
The more you'll have people here, you know, I I can and I let him say whatever what do you want to say?
But then you know, I don't have to sit there and just be abused. I don't have I don't have that's true to I get
And that's and that's and like in people on my show that have felt like
Abused before it's like and I'm sorry, but it's like also
You know like Sigma's Florida diamond like she could have left when he was saying that stuff to her
But she stayed and so
It's like, you know, we can also we can take ourselves out of these situations if we are you know
And so it's not I don't need to necessarily kick somebody off. Oh, I can be really bad, too. You know, yeah
Could be worse than him
Just saying I mean, yeah, I mean, I don't I don't feel like you know, I mean just talking to you now
You're you're very calm person. I don't I don't know. I have to wait to see the other. Oh, I can I can say crazy shit, bro
Okay. Oh, yeah
I put it this way McQueen ran away McQueen ran and ran away from me. So just imagine that
McQueen is like twin brothers. No, it's not like twin brothers. I'm more like his daddy put it that way
You know, I fathered him, let's say, you know, you want to show us a nigga? He's Danny. Um, the little short guy
Yeah
You like this much, okay, I got you you're actually
That's why I muted it for a long time already.
Yeah.
I kind of wanted to see what he said.
But seriously, as for chances, if I really get to the end of my rope with somebody,
if I get to the end of my rope with somebody, I will give them a million chances.
But eventually, I have a limit to things.
more than a good enough reason I bought a gay I bought a guy Amanda and I know I
thought a guy a man and I know around here I can't wait for a leash on Harry
his PhD professor of physics and loves to battle okay Alex moved in and removed
I'm sorry. It's hard to see. I have to read this.
His, yes, woman is here.
Oh, good. His woman, yes, woman is here.
I'm sorry guys. I'm getting kind of tired.
But this is the calmest history I've been in in days.
Okay, so 43 people in chat. What's going on guys?
Anybody have any questions for harry? Well, that's crazy, right? What do people in chat and is the comments the chat bins comes to panel?
Yeah, I don't know. I think nobody's talking. I wonder if that's really 43 people
Or because I someone said oh BKG. Let's lurk. Yeah, I don't know why Alex came in
I think he had beta and Kate are screaming. Who's lurking
Popping the chat a lot of you
There's 47 people in chat and and like four people talking
KZ is there a beat and Kate or be Kate like a cave turtle. Oh sure KZ. KZ you always hop up
I wouldn't mind surprised you over there commenting in the comments
So KZ hey Margie, thank you for being a member. No Harry. Can you do a favorite past?
Can you drop out and come back in see if it fix your mic? I
Don't think it's me. I don't see my avatar move
If I talk like this see it moves
Mine moves. Yeah
Look when I talk, let me see if I take the echo off one side. Okay
One Sam, that's kind of
Others like my head yeah, can you hear me now?
Yeah, see it's kind of echoing a little bit, but it's better. I think it's better than it was. Good morning, CB. How are you?
Testing one two three. Yeah, it works. Now it's sick. It's fine
Didn't echo perfect. It's perfect. I
Can't be distilled be distilled up. I'm surprised you didn't fall asleep. Somehow you lost your fucking beard comb. Oh, oh
Luckily they're not that expensive
Looking between your couch Christians, Brian. You anyone know Brian King? He's a member. Thank you for being members guys Marge martin
Everybody call him BK in the chat though, you heard
Happy Sunday CB
He said yeah, he said in the chat. It's like he said in the chat brankings and they said oh, he's the only five hundred dollars
I don't know why yeah
Nice
Ready, I think he said he'd take $20 though
Because he came a little I don't scared of no I ain't flinching but I'll take a mental note
Okay, okay. I actually have BK tattoo on my chest
Anyone have any suggestions for what the PKG stand for? I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Okay
I like I think I need to save up for the cat tattoo tattoo
Alteration I don't know
Never been called BK online for 30 years. I know you've been called BK. Yeah, so I haven't I so I can cock
I, I tattooed my, I tattooed you, uh, on my chest.
Is it KG, right? Is it KG, right?
BKG, yeah, BKG, uh.
I don't have
Do you really like terror happy because he could read you know dude that freaking evil shit. No, man
Who believes in that stuff? Come on. It's fine
Yeah, he's one of those
Opinion I'll just ask
I'm just saying, you know
Messages okay, got you okay smash. I mean, I think you'll be okay
Do you get possessed you get possessed in order to to read those like
An entity there's an entity into your body and then tell you like oh
See this no the card means that
Like what is it?
Well, basically I have the word I would I just know pull a few cards and then they're they'll have a certain
Meaning or message that might be probably relevant to your past or present. It will tell you how
Maybe you should best approach the future for the best result, but of course you create your future and it's it's up to you
but it basically looks at the present and past energies and
Maybe the best way to proceed forward. It's a good
No chat anybody would like a card
Harry would be great at reading tarot cards. Yeah, I guess, you know, they're really, people are really inspired by my, my, my tarot reading and everyone else is, it can be community starting to get tarot decks.
And Harry doesn't like tarot because he knows that I, I, it reveals the Greeks don't want others didn't achieve anything he claims. Oh, come on.
Now the Greeks are amazing. The Greeks are amazing.
The Greeks probably invented the fucking tarot cards. What is this guy talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about, yeah.
You know, I think, you know, they,
well, they actually, there are like legends of them being from Egypt
and Egypt and Greece are very tied in, you know, of course, they have like,
yeah, there is no such thing as Egypt.
That's just the biblical fucking new term.
but never existed just like Israel never existed the same way Turkey never existed and
It's a new term now and a new people in a new land
You like you it's named renamed. I mean
First go to Turkey and they showed them Greek ruins
You do know that right?
Like they have no history. They have no history all the history that they keep showing everyone around there is Greek
the the the the stadiums the the ruins everywhere the history they have there is all greek and they keep showing us the tourists
making money like greek making money off of greek fucking ruins and greek history like
like it wasn't you know jason and the argonauts they were from from like turkey which would make no sense for the myth
really unless it was like you know part of greece at the time that's why that's how it makes sense that they had the
The that's what I'm trying to tell you their history that they show. Yeah, it's not even theirs. I believe I believe you
I know you know that Persia spoke Greek
You know that right it was a Greek kingdom and then later on taking over and created what what they made
But Persia was a Greek kingdom and they spoke Greek you guys can look that up and see that their first language was Greek
So that means that the kings there and everybody was Greeks. They were not
I'm going to move and hold on, hold on, okay.
Somebody back stage.
Hello.
Yeah, yeah, psyche, you know me.
I've been here a bunch of times.
Okay, hi.
I just want to come off at this guy.
Where does this guy get his source or evidence from
that Greek never, like all these countries never existed.
I mean, I,
Are you just saying nonsense out of your ass and we're supposed to believe you?
No, I'm saying facts. I'm saying facts.
Okay, so facts need evidence and proof. And where's your evidence?
Well, just do your research.
No, no, no, you said it. You just said that Egypt doesn't exist.
Okay, how does Egypt not exist?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Egypt never existed. That place was named Kemet. It was named Kemet.
them it was its original name when you when it's a bit of a lie
Egypt is a biblical lie
It create it was created thousands of years after and in words it never existed
Yeah, okay, so so when you go to Egypt today, and you take pictures of the pyramids
What do you what what is that play you see Greek?
That was the language the Greeks spoke before they came up with Alphabets my friend my friend just focus first
So you're trying to tell me how did the Greek become how did I ask you a question how did the Greek evolve?
How did the Greek evolve?
that's not how did the greek evolve
i asked you a question first
you don't know what you're asking
there's no answer to your stupidity
you're just talking out of your ass bro
you're talking out of your ass
you're talking like a jew
You're talking like a Jew with these Jew fucking gay fucking
Well, that's you know, no, it's talking like a Jew these these
Religion it's not a race you have to understand that
The Jews have written the Jewish people the Jewish people that believe in the Jewish religion
Wrote Christianity and wrote the Muslim religion. They're the ones that created these new religions, you know, and they they're the ones who enslave the
for thousands of years in order to change the history in order to change the history of this planet, you understand?
These are facts I'm speaking to you. Yeah, these are facts. I'm telling you how are they facts because you say they're facts
Do you have any evidence? They are facts because because I've done the research. I've done the research you have
You're just going by whatever your fucking delusional mind can fucking think and whatever
so if you want to do the research on yourself if you want me to do it for you
you know we i can send you like a link you can send me some money and i'll start and i'll start
educating you you made a claim that it doesn't exist but you made it i'm not gonna educate you
i'm not gonna educate you like my ancestors did in the past and made humanity and created what we
have today and then later on i'm shitting on like you are shitting on me right now
you know i am your god you dumb motherfucker there is nothing else
no you're not yes i am your god no you're not my god i'm your god you're just some loser on
the internet i'm your god you dumb motherfucker i am your god i'm everybody's god you're a loser
the greeks are the gods there's nothing else so you believe that the chosen other so you believe
that the chosen are the jews
No, no, no, I don't believe that. I asked you. I asked you. So what do you believe it?
So what do you believe it?
So what do you believe in?
All right, so I don't believe it
Basically, basically, basically it comes down to this. Basically it comes down to this, right? Once you go as far back as you go, right?
You will see that
The only true religion that gave us everything is the 12 God Ideology, right?
That's what gave us absolutely everything we have today, the 12 God Ideology, right?
Nothing came from the religions of today. Nothing came from the religions of today.
Can you give me one thing?
tell me one thing that these religions have given humanity you know the only
thing that this guy's going to do is repeat himself and say blah blah blah
talk talk talk blah blah blah because he is not educated enough and he doesn't
have the skills to educate you understand you see my bloodline was
created to come out and educate the knuckle-tracking neanderthals of the
planet
Yeah, so here I am again thousands of years later educating the Neanderthals of the planet
Are you guys still dragging your knuckles? Yes, a few of you, you know
But you learned how to stand and you're doing much better as humanity bro
You have to answer me. You're just a big mouth. Why don't you answer? Why don't you answer the more important question?
That's not how it works. It's not how it works, bro
You got no answer it is because everything came from the greeks everything came from the greeks
That's why you're not everything from the greeks the greeks created everything you have
You know and then you believe you believe in a jew you believe in a jew and their religion
You believe yeah, but you believe in that that's what it is that places come in
Refer to it as kemen there is no egypt egypt is a new term just like turkey it never existed
do you understand that bro i knew i just think i ran as i ran i ran as a new term i ran as a new
term right it never existed that place was fucking called persia persia right and in order for them
to take away persia the name that i ran persia was a greek kingdom look it up look it up persia
Use that you ever do all of the Middle East all of the Middle East
He hasn't taken a break in there guys. Yeah all of the Middle East
He has not taken a break. You don't know shit. You don't know shit. You don't know shit
Here Harry give me one minute to talk
Go ahead, sir. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it brother. Um, the guy has nothing to say thank you
He doesn't know how to stop. He doesn't know how to stop. I'll let you back out in a minute. Okay. I appreciate it
I appreciate it. Thank you. Yeah, I don't got nothing against the guy, but what I'm saying is
Yes, was it once upon a time called ancient kermit? Yeah, absolutely. I every like for example, uh
Crying out loud. Let's take lebanon lebanon wasn't called lebanon. It was called finicia. Right. Okay. I don't finician's ready to talk about that, right?
Right, right exactly, and it's like for me. I don't care about the name changes what he tried saying is this is his claim
This is the this is literally the only reason I hopped on here and he has yet to answer me
He made a claim right before I came on he made a claim that Egypt Israel and Turkey don't exist
And that is why I hopped on here because I'm like, okay, we'll explain help us understand his answer was no, no, no, you got to do your own research.
Well, no, that's not how discussions work for him.
If you make a claim and someone doesn't understand what you're talking about.
Now it's to be quite honest with you.
I think he's just talking out of his ass.
It's not that I don't understand what he's saying.
He's just because that's what a lot of people are doing on the internet nowadays.
They're just saying what they want people to believe.
Right, they're gonna like okay the new ones psyche. I don't know if you heard this. They're actually, you know all the areas in the Bible
Whether it's Israel or Egypt people are actually trying to say that no no no that's not in the Middle East
That's actually in the United States of America. Yeah. Yeah, I know that was yeah, I've heard this
Egypt is in the US and they've been because the Nile is like the the Memphis River. I mean or something like they
it's kind of ridiculous. There's also a book called Black People Invented Everything,
and it also outlines how Black people invented everything and did everything. And so it's like
you can also pick and choose things and like kind of you can just rewrite people are rewriting history
for themselves these days and then you just pick on these sources they don't know the reputable
sources but they're there's very patriotic Greeks they can say Greeks invented everything
they read the book and it's like oh that's the history.
And now but don't like don't get me wrong psyche. I see in a way where he's going with it as far as like
Like, are we really supposed to trust the higher ups and everything we've been taught and my answer is absolutely not like I do think we've been lied to about a lot of stuff.
And if the good brother says hey like look man I got a download for my for my spiritual guides and they.
This is what they shared with me I will believe him if he's willing to say that. However, just just.
Believe it in your culture too hard, you know I'm saying but you know
The king there was greek
I'm gonna drop off right fucking now if you don't put him in the bag.
We don't do threats, we don't do threats, if you know.
Number one, number one, he doesn't do that.
He doesn't, he's not gonna bring you the views.
He's not gonna bring you the views I bring you.
So it's very fucking disrespectful to fucking put me in the fucking bag.
You understand that?
He's not gonna bring you the views.
Who is that motherfucker?
Huh?
Who is that motherfucker coming up here and attacking me because I'm Greek and I'm better than fucking him and he knows it and he hates me for it.
Number one, let me tell you something. Every fucking place in the Middle East was Greece. Every single fucking one.
The Pharaohs have fucking Mediterranean fucking DNA, which is my fucking DNA, basically fucking from the island creed.
Okay. When you look at the fucking ruins from the Minoan ages and you look at it, it looks like tentacle to what they have in the fucking
in the Middle East. The pillars over there don't look like the modern Greek pillars that they use today.
That's the evolution of the Greek. So because the Greek evolved and changed its, you know,
alphabet and changed its fucking structure of its buildings, you know, it means that it's not the same people.
It means that it's not the same people like if we evolved it means that we're not
We're not we're not the same no more. You're crazy, dude. Let me tell you something when you look up purges fucking
History, you'll see
When you look up Persia's history, you will see that you will see that they spoke Greek in the beginning
You you will see that Troy spoke Greek in the beginning and then later on they changed all this shit
They changed all this information that we see today is all fucking lies. You understand
Look what they're doing with Alexandra the great fucking history and the fucking Muslim population the Albanians
That stole that land over there when the Greeks were enslaved to the Turks
And then they claim in their fucking language and all that shit that they're saying that Alexander the Great was an Albanian now
Some Muslim Albanian that came from Northern Ireland Island and fucking Italy
Nobody knows where these people came from
You know, and that's still in Alexander the Great's fucking history. This is the same way
Great history was fucking taken. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that was Greece
That's Greece, you know
The what's happening all over the fucking
Face today with Macedonia, right? So you're telling me in the Middle East the Greeks were fucking enslaved for thousands of years
You told me that the history of there wasn't changed
We have churches from one end to the next like our orthodox churches when Christianity was established the orthodox churches
We're in the Middle East. They were from one end from from one end from Constantine
So you're telling me that the Greek didn't establish all that over there before even even though after the new religions the Greek was still there
Yeah
Somebody said Harry you ain't better than anyone all your facts are wrong and you ain't all my facts is factual all the facts are factual
It's really true. You don't bring I don't bring you. Yeah, I know that's fucking faggots all talking fucking lies, bro
You know that that is lies everybody. I already proved it wherever I go
There's your eyes and there's action
So that's fucking ridiculous and in order for them to fucking say that you know that it's the total opposite
you know, that's facts
Everywhere I go people come to fucking see so I don't give a fuck. It's the facts, you know
Go look at go look at some of shit whenever when I went there
That's when some of shit fucking went to like seven or eight hundred
abuse
Before that they were just hitting like three four or two
Five always I went there when they went to eight
It went to a plus and I don't know what happened
I guess they were fucking sharing the shit and when you share your shit too much
You know your fucking views start to go down your fucking shit gets
Monetized or whatever happens happen to me too my views don't go up anymore. I should have had thousands of views
I'm one of the most
Fucking
Conferential people that you could come across so everyone wants to see who the fuck is this president
I fucking told this guy's nuts. Let me fucking go. So they would all come to my fucking channel to just see who I am
you know so i've never seen you have a live stream
i've never seen you have a live stream and your views is not that high papa
i know that's what i'm trying to tell you that they should be you understand
because i shared because i shared a lot of my fucking videos on um
On platforms I shouldn't have, I got fucking monetized
and my views don't go up anymore.
They just stay stable, like they just don't go up.
No matter how many times you'll go view a video,
it will not move, it'll just stay in that number,
it just will not go up, you know?
Because I fucking shared it on Strava,
I shared it on a few fucking other places
where I shouldn't have done, you know?
Like a fitness app, like...
the
That would be a good thing, right?
Like, if they feel that they can do anything better,
they can come up here and fucking talk, you know?
But what I have to say is factual, you know?
And if you could fucking prove me wrong, you know,
with what, your fucking stupidity,
you're gonna prove me wrong with your fucking dumb shit,
which are lies.
And you know that all the literature
that exists today comes from BlackRock.
You do know that, right?
You know one company writes all the literature around the world. They control everything you people fucking know, you know
so once you once you do your research within there within if
You look if you look at anything you Google, right? It'll say edit it and it'll be edited really recent
Recently it'll say edited last week today yesterday an hour ago
Like what are you editing? What do you what do you guys keep changing here?
Why is this keep changing?
Go look go look for yourselves go Google anything you want and then go all the way to the end and see where it says edited and
See when the motherfucker was edited. It'll be so recent. Why do they keep chipping away at the information taking shit out?
Why?
You know because they've been burying Creek fucking shit all the time. Who is controlling the world?
the biggest enemy of the greek was a jew why don't you see the greek in any of the religions of today
do you hear of the greek in it we established this planet how the f*** do the religions not have
us in it we established everything roads schools kitchens windows buildings anything you want
to f***ing think about we did it we did it how the f*** are we not in the f***ing books
And they have the Romans which came way later, which was just another Greek fucking kingdom look up that the Romans who spoke Greek
Rome was built by the Greeks
There was no fucking
Italian came way later Italian is a new breed of people that was made through spanish
Listen to me dickhead. I'm just that I'm just educating you if you want to get
that came out, you know, like a fucking professor, you know, I know that I can tell you one thing,
right? The information that I'll give you is 10 times fucking better than any professor. I'll tell
you that. No fucking professor could teach you what I could teach you. No fucking professor.
And what I teach you is the facts and truth. I'm not telling you no fucking black rock fucking
You understand the other people used to fucking enslave it those religions of today enslaved it using the Greek
Using Greek fucking knowledge. They would go into an indigenous land, right and tell them oh, I can if you guys don't listen to me
I'm gonna block the Sun and they would use the eclipse to fucking enslave a whole population
Because they weren't educated and then the Greek gave education to the planet
And that's how the Greek gave light and set the world free
You understand that's why an Easter, right that thing that they do has nothing to do with Easter has nothing to do
With Christianity nothing the light that they give on Easter to pass around the world on the greek orthodox fucking
Christianity was the light that the greek gave to the planet to free it from the fucking evil sons of bitches that are fucking
Slaveing us today
That was that's all that is it's not has nothing to do with the Christianity at today
Yeah, that ritual was to
Was was the light the Greeks gave to the planet? That's what that means the knowledge we gave
The free everybody which I think was the biggest mistake we ever made because look at us now. You understand
That's what I think of the Neanderthals, you know when there's a there's a saying and it goes
Familiarity familiarity breeds contempt
you understand
before you guys familiarized yourselves with your gods
you understand because you got too familiar with us
and then we lost our godliness, we lost our power, we lost everything
so familiarity breeds contempt and that's what fucking happened
between the gods and the fucking gentiles
and you understand, that's what happened
You guys got to familiar with us
You guys
they are numbers. The numbers are the same.
Well, well, what do you make it so funny?
We're not on a platform.
We're not on a platform where, you know, there's fucking,
you know, hundreds of thousands of fucking people.
Nobody in the back? Nobody in the back?
Shut up. No, I just, but I do want to,
I want to do this greeting real quick for...
Okay, we got a reading, people.
JT just wanted a card. Okay.
Okay, seven of coins. Okay, so the seven of coins. Okay
This is like, you know, he's been planting something growing something it says you have a long
Road ahead of you and are working hard to set yourself up for success
Seven of coins and buys you to make decisions with long-term in mind careful planning
Will lead to rewards in the future. So I hope that was helpful
Let's see. Oh, yeah, he's back. Okay. Hello. Yeah, so I can give you give me one sec. I got a connection. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Okay. So more than just live. Welcome back. Thank you live.
And I do know you know like a lot of people don't know the Bible the New Testament was written in Greek
Right in the Old Testament maybe in Hebrew, but they both come from I think Phoenician the alphabet comes from based on the Phoenician alphabet
Which was like
Sailors were they from where the Phoenicia around Greece or in Greece just another Greek kingdom
Just another Greek kingdom
You see what happened was this the the the the atomic bomb at the time to control the population, right?
Was the alphabet whoever came up with the alphabet was going to control the population, right?
so and there was hundreds of great kingdoms and their
like
Socrates or a play-doh or you know the advisor everyone was always of each kingdom was
at war with each other to find who was going to come up with the best fucking alphabet
and the alphabet that we use today is the one that won, you understand, and that kingdom
is the one that became the greatest Greek kingdom amongst all Greek kingdoms.
So hey, Mr. Greek, let me ask you this.
You know, you're saying a lot of stuff
I'm educating you bro, I'm educating you man
But you know, you keep overstepping me
I agree with you
Because I'm giving you the answers
I'm giving you the answers
To all the fucking riddles
Can you pass the mic?
This is what I want to say to you, right?
I agree with what you're saying
About ancient Greek history
Now, for the record
There are some things called methyl mythology, right?
So you got like
Oh, I want to, I want to, I want to point this out fast.
Um, you know how you respect, uh, beta?
I mean come on, bro. What do you like a two-year-old? Is it that really important? You got to cut somebody off?
Can't you wait your turn, bro? Jesus Christ
Anyways, man, anyways, man, this one's saying right I agree with what this guy's saying the Greek guy
I don't disagree with what he's talking about the ancient Greek history
What he's not understanding is there's a reason why there was a downfall
Right and now I don't need to get too much into but here's one bro karma right karma gain you back for not doing
What you're supposed to be doing?
So you want to talk all this shit about how your people were superior to all of us and blah, blah, blah
But you're not mentioning the gods that punished you for a reason because you guys fucked up
You weren't supposed to fuck up and you did because if you didn't fuck up
You'd still be kings and queens like you say you are anyways. That's all I wanted to say to him
But I'll I'll stay on the panel. I want to see what he's got to say. Okay
There's a difference. We weren't kings. We were gods. You understand
Correct
Children of the most high
Can't man somebody put your picture up there. Yeah, I
Thank you, don't complain can't don't complain with somebody put your picture on like these. All right, just saying
Thank you
Yeah, well, this is a flattering photo of myself
Anyway, I'm sorry guys
Yeah, I think you guys are you know, I come into like some kind of understanding like, you know
Well, I just want to know I want to know
Do you agree you guys were punished do you agree you were punished though?
No, we were repunished. We were we were taken over that's all punish for what?
From being
Okay, if you go from
Isn't that a punishment? How is it? How is that? How is it?
Because I'm saying
And you no longer have it and you no longer have it. I was
You need everything. You need everything. I don't need anything. No, I don't I practice a lot of detachment
I practice a lot of detachment. What what does a god need?
Bro, are you gonna just keep yelling over me? Ask a question. You just say stupid shit
Okay, ask a question. Ask a question and I would have thought ever fucking become a bump. How could that possibly be?
So I'll answer you so I'll answer you so when you say that you guys had everything you're a hundred percent right
But I said we gave you everything and never said we had everything we gave you know
So we gave the world everything you had a we gave the world everything we gave the world absolutely everything
Yes, did you have ancient knowledge?
Yes, you know, of course, we had all the knowledge.
There is no other knowledge.
This world only has Greek knowledge.
Oh, what do you mean?
Ancient knowledge is modern knowledge is ancient knowledge.
What's the difference?
Well, the difference is there's no such thing as ancient American knowledge
because America's a new one.
Yeah, but but to get here to get there, you needed to.
You know follow one process with a Greek process my friend
America is laid out on on Greek on Greek
I'm talking about that's not what you know that you know that America is based on Greek layout
You do know that right? I mean in every way, you know
America's natural land. It's not based on anything you want it to be based on
I'm talking about the idea of America and what and how it came about, you know, it's based on Greece. You do know that, right?
Like that's what it comes out. You do know that right and you do know that they were about to like when they were voting
What language they were gonna put here
It was either Greek or English and they said that Greek lost by one vote and you do you know that that was a lie, right?
That that the English fucking rats
Just stole that shit. You do know that but you can look up this fucking information yourself. You don't need to believe me
you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you
No, not too many would you don't let anybody answer like I'd love to answer your question
I think you're very intelligent. No cap. I think you're a very highly gifted
IQ
intelligent human being but you you know, you're very passionate. That's what it is and I appreciate that. I'm just sick and tired
I'm sick and tired
Well, I love the Greeks. I love the Greeks. I got no problem with the Greeks
It's that's kind of what you're not like feeling. I don't even give a fuck that I'm Greek
I just came to this conclusion because I did research and I'm not saying this shit because I'm Greek
I would have said this shit. I
Looked at the planet as an alien. I didn't even look at it as I didn't know all the shit
I know
You know, I didn't know but if you think and start using your own logic and common sense
You'll come to the same conclusion
I mean, there's no way I mean, how is it that all the other kingdoms spoke Greek and they were all all spoke in Greek that language is Greek
Established by Greeks and then all of a sudden it's not great. How is this and how is that?
Macedonia right now has been taken over by a bunch of Muslim fucking
Albanians and have China still fucking out gender of great fucking history
And then they had fucking Hollywood Jews create a fucking movie to prove that
Give me what I gotta give me one quick. Yeah, I like Alexander the great they don't like to mention that he's
What he's uh, you know, he's Greek he's Greek and he's um, I
Mean he's got I think what was it the record again? I think he's got the most wins on the front lines
I believe something like that
Yeah, yeah, something like that, but he's got he's got a world record. That's for sure. He's got some great
I don't know if we can even believe all the information they tell us man. I'm telling you. I agree, brother
I agree with you. Nothing they've told us is true. Nothing. We they've been telling us is true
I mean, they've told us that we went to the moon. I mean you believe that shit
I mean we can't even leave the atmosphere and they tell us we went there and then all of a sudden they told us
Okay, we've lost all the technology. We don't know how to go there no more like what?
Like, wait, wait, wait, we know how to get there, and back then and now all of a sudden
we don't know how to get there.
You destroyed all the fucking information.
What?
Like, what are they saying to us, you know?
They gotta be fucking shitting us.
So then, now you're gonna believe what they've written about the Greeks that were enslaved
for thousands of years, first by the fucking Persians, then by the fucking Romans, then
by the Turks.
I mean, the Turks only had them for 500.
But this is a long fucking time of fucking slavery. Why do you think that happened was to destroy the 12-god ideology that created this planet?
To destroy the true fucking chosen so the fucking people today can be looked at as the chosen with their fucking fake religions that they wrote
With the burning bushes and part of the fucking seas you understand?
That's that's mythology bro. That's mythology at least a fucking Greek proof something
We proved some some factual shit and gave people shit, you know, what do these guys do other than what they're doing right now?
Put your in and fucking creating war that's all they do they didn't fucking can do nothing else
What have what have the religions of today given us I can't think of one fucking thing
And
Religion is like a it's like a way to control control populations. You know, it's the way to absolutely absolutely
Absolutely, it's like it's like it's like a bigger a bigger
You know the way that they use sports to divide us within the country
They use religion to divide us within countries, you know, yeah within continents. Yeah, that's what they do
So the religion is just a creation
of like gangs it's like they create gang you know and each gang is gonna end up killing each other
and that's what they gotta do now they make it look like it's a good thing like the like
it's a religion the gang and I mean like that gang they make it look like it's a reason to be
You know, they couldn't be the only ones they couldn't be the only ones so the ones that believe in bow
They couldn't be the only ones to look that way. So they created other ones through religion
To look the way as they do
They couldn't be the only fucking big dang trying to take over and that's the gang that took over
Rome the one that took over Greece the one that took over, you know
The one that is in the Middle East right now causing the fucking havoc
That's the same gang that fucking toppled every fucking empire in the past
and every time they toppled it, they passed their fucking
hermaphrodite god ideology, you know, that's why you see like, you know, satanism is their fucking
ideology. The hermaphrodite that you see satanists with a half goat and half a human, that is their god bow.
That is bow.
Oh, you know and who fucking believes in it those people right there. They are look it up
It'll see the Israelite when and believed in and fucking bow bow was that guy and you know, and then later on they got
Bobby's Bobby's Lord. I mean, it's they are yes, Bobby's Lord. And so there's like, you know, ba-ba-la ba-ba-la and there's just about and there's like
Like a lot of but it was also like a tie. It was a kind of a title
And so they put it like you know what it's Moloch and like, you know the rapper night in a Satanism is back from that
But yeah, you're right. It's also a k a ball. It's like, you know, Lord. Yeah
Yeah, so that's that's the people right now that are basically running our planet
You know pushing this idea and if you see that's where first like the idea of
of homosexuality and
Like
the trans, the idea of trans and stuff came from this.
These are the people who are pushing this.
And these are the people who pushed it in Rome.
They're the people who pushed it in Greece.
They're the people who pushed it in America right now.
You know, these are the same people who believe in that.
And that's why each empire, every time they got toppled,
they'd fucking have this fucking horrific history
of this shit happening.
You know what I'm saying, and then they're like all fucking pointing at the whole population saying oh, yeah
They were all fucking transvestites look at them. You know meanwhile it was this
Same people that are that toppled America and have been pushing their fucking
Statistic ways here
You know, it's the same fucking people that they did it to every empire and then they fucking end up right in the history
What what type of history you think America's gonna end up with with with with with whatever the trans shit
That's happening with the children and all this shit. What do you think's gonna happen?
Well history ends up repeating and stuff and you know we've been through cycles of culture like culture revolutions
And then they're followed by this really really
Morning guys
Yeah
I mean, but I mean, I do find it interesting, you know, I love Greek mythology, I do love Greek mythology on my channel, and it's, you know, mythology, philosophy, mathematics and ways of thinking and writing alphabets and I mean, they did do so much.
Society forever, you know, I mean, it's like it's the same thing. It's like
Is that amazing civilization and wonderful things came out of it?
You know, we don't necessarily know all the whole story that happened, but
You know history is written by the people in charge. We have to have
Look at different sources. Some people have different theories, but
Right, but you know, just like but I'm glad you you know, you appreciate your culture and it's always good to have some pride in
If you're a cultural heritage and, you know, you should be proud because you're a cultural heritage.
I'm just trying to, like, you know...
everything's confused everything that we know is not is not what it is
I'm letting you know that that everything that we know is not what
It's not true. You know, I mean if they're they're trying to convince some of the population right now that there's you know
Flat Earth and why are they doing this? It's just another division that they're causing mentally
You know just to divide us to argue about some nonsense. So we don't fucking focus on what's really
More important, you know, like why should we fucking even spend a minute arguing if the world is flat, you know
I'm saying that it's just crazy or if there's a big foot, you know
Or if the fucking Locknick monster fucking exists all these are distractions constantly, you know the aliens, you know
I mean what they they turned around and said that we were supposed to fuck. I mean
Who was it some fucking Israeli general?
Went to Mars with the aliens, you know, and that Trump fucking knows about the aliens. Yeah, like
Then all of a sudden they stopped with that shit
Yeah
they will make it for them
because they knew they would make it for them
exactly
they tested for storylines, they see the public reaction
and they continue pushing it out
or they just may try to make it look ridiculous
to throw everybody off the biggest
but let me tell you something
that to me was terrifying
and I'll tell you what
because I feel that
if they think that we're that stupid
You know, like what are they about to do to us? Are they about this planet telling us the greatest lies like you know
They got the fucking nukes
I don't know.
The Satanists are like, basically they see human beings, or the major breed of the population
as animals, like to herd and to, you know, you as cattle, and then they're the gods,
and they're the wild animals, and then they don't look like people as humans, or they
don't even see themselves as humans, they see themselves as something else as humans.
I don't know whether they're gods or demons, but definitely they see us.
they see us as soulless beings that don't have no soul, you know, and that
they tell us they tell us that they know we do have a soul
but they tell us we don't and we kind of can forget
and or you know we can like or well well they tell themselves
they tell themselves that we do that there is we don't have one so they don't
No, they just I mean they don't feel bad because they're kind of psychopathic and they don't have empathy
Right, exactly. Yeah, right, right serial serial killers. That's what they really are
Yeah, oh man, I mean there's many different times
Yeah, basically that's on the philosophy, you know, it's very it can be humanistic in certain ways
But then you get into it. It's very like anti-human and
And kind of cruel and I don't like to see I like to look see all humans as human beings
You know all you know imperfect yet, you know
Incredible incredible individuals and not your gods and animals or something like that. It's first into a human petting zoo, right?
It
Supposed nothing, but it horseshit then the government about everything. Yeah, I mean, it's like yeah
We're like the moon landing if you watch the moon landing
You know, there's a press conference. They had afterwards
if you watch the press conference you know i'm showing bozaldrin look very confused they look nervous they look right right yeah and it's like and
they don't have the right details about even anything that happened there they were saying
oh there's three the stars in the moon we should have been able to i mean so
but there's stories they didn't match
and it's also a hot story they didn't match
that Van Allen belt is impossible to get through that Van Allen belt
There's no way to it's like too powerful to go through, but they somehow made it through right?
They're the only one the only the one time I mean why haven't we been back since so easy to go what about the sun flares?
What about the sun flares?
Solar flares. Yeah, that will they affect the solar flares those things will fucking cook them in that freaking thing
You know what I'm saying? It's just impossible and then you know when when they were questioning the
Astronauts, I forgot and really better names, but they were questioning the astronauts, right the ones that landed or whatever, right?
and they were asking him the same questions and both of them had totally different answers.
One of them said they had to warm up the cockpit because whatever it was, the area that they're
inside the spaceship, they had to warm it up because it was so cold in space. And then
the other one said that it was so hot that we had to cool it down. They had totally different
Yeah, so it was all lies, you know, and the footage that they're showing us is just all fucking also fake, you know
But they're playing every time playing golf on the moon. They're playing golf
They're writing right under in a rollercoaster. They're putting their masonic flag down. I mean, they're just doing yeah
It's an insane thing. Yeah, first they were doers. They were barely briefed on what to keep
Confidential because of threat. Well, okay guys watch a movie called capital four one
It's about a man-mission to Mars.
Okay, since we have a man-mission to Mars,
and right before the astronauts are about to take off to go to Mars,
they get ushered out of the shuttle, and they're like,
by a government official, they get to a secret place.
They're like, they got seen a movie set of Mars,
and they're like, hey, it's way too dangerous to actually send you to Mars,
and so we're just going to pretend, you know, pretend,
and then we'll film the Mars landing here, and then we'll,
but yeah, so you have to take out that movie.
You know what I think area 51 talking about like the landing area 51. I believe is where they filmed it
That's why they don't allow anyone to go there. Nothing ever landed over there
I feel that that is where they filmed the moon landing and if anyone goes at the rock
They'll recognize like the the the landscape, you know, so they'll be like holy shit
This looks like the moon landing over here, you know, so that's why they don't allow anyone to go there
But area 51, that's what I believe it was, you know
Yeah, they're never gonna say anything, but I just can't think it to myself. Why is that fucking place gated off?
What landed there nothing if it did who cares like why do they have the whole area we gated off?
Like didn't they remove it like why what it makes no sense?
You know what they said to us just a little bit of thinking it's just because when we when we
Well, we were born here, you know, we were, we believed everything we were told, you know, we were brainwashed with children, you know, to believe in this place.
God bless America, freaking praying to this fucking flag every morning, you know, so it's like, you had more trust in your government than your own parents.
Then when you start to fucking think for yourself and see what things are really, you know, you're like, oh my God.
You know, yeah, yeah, it's worse than it's worse than you'll ever fucking believe
because government is
Governmental and so government that you can control and meant though is the mind and so government may be my control basically
It's basically not controlling the mind of people
So just keep them, you know, basically for a good reason and for bad reason
It's like because it's nice to have an easily controllable population
Yeah for the higher ups and
and have them program, and also, you know, you can program people, actually for good or evil, they actually do program people for evil, too.
They did the whole rap industry based on programming to inner cities to be violent and sell drugs and things like that, right?
Yeah.
I mean, it doesn't matter how much money they make, they still create some type of bad criminal record or something.
I mean look look at some of the fucking athletes too the athletes still uh
They turn around with some kind of criminal record
No matter how much money they make they're like criminals. It doesn't matter
I so you figure it out. I don't know what's happening really, you know
Why would somebody why would somebody need to be a criminal when they make millions? I don't know
I don't know yeah
You can invest in like illegal enterprises and stuff like that
You know you can you know you can use legitimate money like for illegal things and like you know
You can buy like a lot of drugs with the money you make from the basketball and then
Generations this didn't happen when like our generation back in the day, you know like
Michael Jordan's times and a little bit past that
these guys were respectable they were like freaking gentlemen you know they
carried it with themselves really uh respectfully and had you know good
respectful jobs they didn't cheat on their wives and then fucking you know i mean
they were respectable people i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know how to
I don't know about that, you know, from Babe Ruth, Magic Johnson, many, many professional athletes have been notorious cheaters on their wives, but yeah, there was like a lot of very respectable, but you know, nowadays they have the guy, who's the guy, he's in the Colorado basketball team, and he was in a strip club twice, waving around a gun with his stripper and stuff, having pictures taken of him, right?
Yeah, we're talking about criminals.
Criminals. Yeah, I mean, I mean, it's like sometimes they emulate criminals, but they're not it's kind of like even when like
One you see if you
Everyone wants everyone wants to have this like criminal background. You know, it's like they're gonna be the cool one
You know, I'm gonna I have a criminal background
And I don't know that's the mentality that we we have today, you know
That's the culture like it's like, okay, so
It's like it's like so if you give a criminal background that will give you street cred if you want to do like a rap album
Or be it be it do rap but once you're once you have all the money from the rap album like most of the time
They you know they'll buy a nice house and they'll in a nice area and they'll have a gated community and I'll send their kids to private school
and uh, they will um
You know and they'll keep and they won't let their kids listen to any of their music, you know, and it's like
They'll be legitimate because it's like you don't want to be in danger of going to prison when you're like
You know millionaire and stuff and so they're here to keep their hands pretty clean
I think but yeah, so they feel like to like look tough cool or connected or doing something edgy or illegal
I don't know. It's like it's very glamorized in our society that the whole crime all the organized crime and
It's very glamorized in movies the Hollywood and people just think oh, that's cool, but it's very
It's very bad for the world, it's very bad for the world, it's a long run.
It's a shame that we imitate the media, instead of the media being based on our behavior,
the media does the behavior and we imitate the media's behavior.
You know what's fucked up, that these people are representing America actually.
you know that's what the world sees a bunch of criminals as actors athletes fucking singers
entertainers oh fucking bunch of criminals like it's it's like okay let me go become a fucking actor
so I could like boost my fucking drug company you know like I don't know that it's like I don't
it's like, they don't become an athlete to get out of fucking drug dealing
it's like, like, they're gonna go become a fucking super athlete
so they'll fucking get a, to boost their drug fucking company
you know?
yeah
that's how I see things, cause
They're not stopping it. They're not fucking changing their life. You know, they're just fucking enhancing it in that and in that end
A lot of politicians a lot of politicians who are very you know, like it looks like respectable people for most of the time
Usually they're compromised
individuals, you know with their being puppets for somebody else and
With the money they get like, you know, there's certain people like sir. I won't say any names, but they would
You know they get some money from the president. They make way more money from
Some illegal probably a lot of illegal ventures some legal some illegal the summer record is all that I that was
It takes to get rich. What is where's your millions? Oh my gosh, funny, bruh
Yeah, I mean, but some you know, there are there are people with criminal records that are you know
I think the guy that owns like fat burger. He was a prisoner and he's done he because he owned fat burger, but
so it's possible to
change and re-realitate
the
You know once once they change and they change for the better the rest of them stop pointing the finger laughing at them
I go look at the softy over here. Yo, oh shit. This guy look he turned on us, man
Look at him. Yo, what do you got about water gun? Oh shit. Look, bro. You got a water gun on him, man
You know what I'm saying so then so then you know, I mean the guy can't get pussy
Because he fucking became fucking more normal and became more of a normal human being of society
So now you can't get pussy. Everyone looking at him like he fucking is some kind of pussy himself. So
What is he gonna do? He starts the fucking dog again. Fuck that shit. Yo, I'm running shit up in here
You know not me and then all of a sudden he's in jail
because
You have to keep a fucking
Reputation of being a fucking criminal
So you can get pussy
Yeah
And then I can look but a lot of the good that love this stuff in like rap video
It's like a lot of it is like so glamorized and it's like to make it look attractive
And it's just some people in that music so it's like hypnotic too, but
It's like, it's just basically just to program the young people to fill up the prisons and you know, support this prison
What's it called? I don't know. There's the whole the whole prison system
It's a long it needs to be filled and a company owns it actually I think this company had to do with creating rap
Oh
Joe you look at you just you look mad at me Joe. You look so mad. I don't want you to yell at me and say the N words
I'm afraid
I see backstage looking at me. Joe's bad at me. Are you mad? He's but Joe you look so mad. Why you look so mad?
He's actually just mad. Oh my gosh
Modge is looking mad at me too right now. Oh here look. I'll bring him up. I'll bring him up
Thank you. I'm happy. I'll be quiet. I'm happy. I'm not being okay. Okay. No, no, no
Feeling so slight when you would let me up. Yeah, I've always been nice to you. I've never maybe one time I was rude
No, it's just like I was
It's like you're mad at me. I was scared. You think you're here yelling at the camera
Never be mad at you. So you got to never be in bed about this friend, okay?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry if I was like you know, a little bit
I remember that song somewhere over the rainbow where that fat the wine guy sang it like
Where is that it threw his fat the wine ashes into the lake
I don't remember that part where he did that
Yeah, that was like 400 pounds
Was that, well I'd say 405
Is that when he died?
Yeah, he died. He was 500 fucking pounds. Of course he died. I mean in that video they show him putting the ashes of him somewhere
Yeah, they don't yeah, they don't show him dying, but they show his family like dumping his asses
I'm not making fun of him. I actually cried when I seen this they dump his asses like into like a lake or something
Yeah, well, let's take you know, and he was so fat. It was like 20 pounds of ashes. It was like so many fucking ashes
Yeah, like God
Well, and why are you mentioning that I?
Love you psyche. No, are you mentioning that though like what's the point of like
Somewhere drips like lemon drafts
Okay. Yeah, I love the Judy Garland version, but that yeah, that you could really version is not bad
Version when Judy sings it that's the best it was the device version come on boys
Yes, what your camera's a little blurry. Is there anything on the camera?
How's it looking now
Alright have a look at that, buddy. I thought it would just like I do appreciate you let me up here
I know I can be very aggressive very annoying, but thank you
Yeah, I'll be okay. I just I think I'm kind of rough couple days
You know, I know you're worried you get attacked every time you let guests up here
I know you're I know you're on your your wits are wearing out. You're on your friend's hand man. I know what you're
I'm just I'm just it's just like you get kind of a fatigue. Yeah, I get poor bomb fatigue. It's like, oh
again
I know but it's like even like not poor mom's they're just like people's like you think doing the
language bombs and doing other stuff and I think I'm just trying to like hey, I'm just trying to like talk and
You know
Yeah, you're just a good guy just chillin up man. Yeah
Thank you
Joe fresh out of church after a couple drinks. Yeah money crops humans. Well, yeah, they're saying
they're saying
The the root of evil is the love of money
It's like the love of loving loving money better than his money's just a mature thing. It's like it's not like
You have all the money the world, but it won't buy you happiness, right? It won't take your friends or sad feelings away
Not you. I mean my bad feelings. Oh, I mean
And I do have money saves don't make me happy I feel feel
There's very happy
like, you know
Fishermen in the beach on Thailand. There's very sad billionaires, right? And so, you know, we have you know, it doesn't matter
You know, it's it's I guess how you feel
Yeah
Thank you, brother and now you were saying and the best the best things in life are not things, right?
The best thing in life is waking up and realizing I was born in America. That's what I love. Oh
God bless America
I could turn out
Yeah
No, we're quite quite interesting
I was born in Michigan. She was born in Michigan. She was born in Michigan, Joe
I was born in Michigan. That's right. That's where good times is from. Holy shit
They should meet up and that's
Good times. Oh, yeah, you should meet up and kiss good times, please. Hi, Mikey
Mikey
Good times the good times was kind of a jerk yesterday to me, so
the
It comes down to love and that's what I love
Joe it was so funny crystal reason chat and and then
He was like saying I don't know how I mentioned but you know, she's on the show last night. She was
And she and she and she's like I wasn't on your show last night and like I guess you were you want and and she's like
I was not and she was and everyone else was like in the chat was like yes
He did and she don't remember. We saw you Chris. So you were here
Yeah, lie Chris though we saw you we literally saw you Chris with her own two eyes
Yeah
But I'm gonna say what they right now. If you want to attack crystal you're gonna have to go through me boy
I don't attack so the thing is I've never attacked crystal
But she she excuses me saying like the worst things about her that I've never said I wouldn't even say it
I told you one thing yesterday, but she also said that
I would call her a crack whore and I don't I've never called anybody that like I don't use that kind of language
I don't I don't like that's not a vocabulary really crack whore
So how I don't know what she's thinking. I'm saying these things. I don't know
Crack whore. No, that's what she accused me of calling her
And I did that she got right I get her cheese. Yeah, I'll give you a tank
Yeah, I know I would not at a time of vocabulary to call people though. Okay, so I did all Chris
They'll grow up slice a good guy. He's not attacking you
Now people can get people can get
Things first personally or take things the wrong way. It's easy to take things the wrong way the internet or misunderstand
I wish I could pet your little I wish I could pet that pussy. I wish I could pet that little puss
all my god, okay, you're gonna rabbit by the neck you don't gotta have it by the
point that I'm not grabbing around the neck I'm
She looks fine. He's not struggling for air. He's not
No, he's not what did I say she?
He's all look. He looks fine. He looks fine guy just hold him up by the furl. Oh
Come on
Oh, you know how Michael Jackson Michael Jackson was like held his baby over the over the Braille at everyone like was like
This baby blanket he's like
That baby
No, but yeah, and we're Jordaned
That's not that's not a lyric
Say like I were Jordan
Why can't fucking on Harry talk Harry tanks. How did you fall asleep Harry? Oh
Just allowing you guys to have a conversation
Okay
If I was what you know Joe? No, no, that's Joe. That's Harry
No, no, I got one move. Okay, I'm gonna be a shoe
I'm gonna shove this entire thing on my ass all in about one. Oh my god. Oh my god
Hey CB
But I couldn't find a good place to put this fucking thing. Oh my god, dude
Anybody can I borrow some Vaseline anybody got some back
That's a huge
I'm finally allowed off and this is what I'm doing. So I gotta apologize. You finally
I'm gonna shut my fuck up my ass. Well, don't do it on a camera. Just do it on camera
No, of course, I won't do it on camera, buddy. Yeah
Go up put it in and they come back up here right now
We just want to hear the sound
Yeah
Michael Jim next what I am
I'm a model gymnast
Okay
I don't go to other streams and chat in other streams. I'm kind of like
Watch your watch your talk watch your I'm not going I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm not going anywhere because I'm not
I'm not really welcome anywhere anymore. So you're bad. You're bad. I'm bad for everywhere. So
Just for saying that you're bad. Okay. Oh my god. Yes for fucking even thinking of saying that
Hmm finally was a cracker
Where do you get all the money? Where do you put the blood charge?
Where do you put the blood charge?
Well, let's see
Why so early? Oh, this guy's driving here. Why yeah, why so horny why so horny guys?
Why so early, dude?
Yeah, whatever he said why so horny. I'm not horny. I'm looking at you
Well, then you must be horny if you're looking to meet with I'm completely soft
That's not basically like you basically look at it Ben Affleck
OK.
I'll meet Joe Applack from now on.
Thank you.
You look like Danny Bonaducci.
If you think of Fat Danny Bonaducci, I'm just gonna remember when Bob Levy remember when Bob Levy like smack Danny Bonaducci in the face
Like for like content. That was fun with Bob or Danny Bonaducci
Smell or no Bob Levy smacked Danny Bonaducci. Oh
Hi Ruth
the
Yeah, but you know what also I did I got my own chin McPanel boys. Did you get modded? I don't think so
Wow, so
What are you doing you're trying to hit a record of drinking and
Panelling like let me see how many
Beers I could do in how many hours I can panel
Like he remember Cal Ripkins record. I want to join
2600 straight panels for every day like Cal Ripkins and break the record of the other event
He was a panelist
Yep, I'm going to be the iron horse of the panel. I'm going to join for seven thousand things
What about sleeping stuff?
You know what Ashley now don't even worry about sleep is like what about changing your final shirt. What about that?
What about that? Well, that's going yesterday, so I'll change it today. Oh
Is that your costume? That's like your little YouTube costume nice nice
I didn't know that people had costumes when they were doing YouTube
It's like a flail, it's kind of like a...
I wear it over my shirt because it's a war when I went on a bike
I'm like, yeah, I'm only saying that
Show me your costumes, I keep showing me your costumes
The one that, uh, what do you guys get?
Oh, don't you dare show me your colored buttons
Show me your costumes
This guy wants costumes
I'm not wearing it
You want costumes?
Huh?
We're not wearing it right now, folks
It's in the house. Why are you watching like why are you getting all right? What are you doing with your hands? What the hell is that?
Is that a Johnny's bedtrap?
Harry Harry do you want to see uh you want to see me in my studio?
Yeah, this guy definitely
Show him show him speed oh man
Show them you're a pride American
I'm not wearing underwear right now
Oh
You'd like when I rollin around
So I just find my toes. I don't know anything about reaction. Oh, you don't okay your courage. You've got plenty you
Okay, okay
Oh, look at the tricks
3F
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't
Joe writes a skateboard and he goes to this guy next to Mr. Wilson's house and
Yeah, you're Dennis the men's adult
Yeah, I'm about 80 years old right now
that
tell, tell him to terracotta
what your angle's behind you is
I'm afraid I'll be too, it's too sexy for YouTube
so I'll just show, I'll just show it to the whole
yeah, thank you
yeah, that's a big deal
Dennis the Menace would make a slingshot
out of your fucking speedo
uh, that's your joke
that's really what you got to say, buddy
Hey
Dennis you can use that as a face mask bro. Yeah, yeah, that should be a face
Right like that. I'm wearing it
Summer remember that ladies summer to join inside that her panties are real. I
Yes, I remember summer
Summers panties smell like
I
Keep going put it on
Yeah, no, you want me to play a Harry really?
I do I do I will
Easy gonna get his money's worth out of these videos
I don't know what is that I'm gonna be I'm gonna be clipped. You love it. He said I did whoever's right there Katrina
I said do it. She said abroad said it do it do it
Well
share your path
share what?
I want Harry to see us
it's not your
come on Katrina, it's Saturday night
Sunday morning please
share a little gumption
hey
he's doing it, see dog
he's gonna come back with a fucking thong
Joe I'm not doing it for you
I'm doing it for Harry okay
I
I actually can't see anything
but I'm just listening
I listen to the reaction people
he's pretty shiny like he can't see
he can see, this guy's lying
I really can't, I have no idea what's happening
nevermind
is Joe still there?
Joe see me in my speedos a thousand times
he did?
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Hey Joe
What are you looking at Joe show do you see anything?
Um, I don't see anything. That's the problem. I don't see it. Don't stop looking. It's the American flag
What's that looking? Yeah, he was looking he saw everything
Not I see it. I smelled it. I can see it and know it. Thank you. It smells. It smells delicious
This guy's breaking playing with his Kilbasa
No, I'm right here. I'll put the kelbasa away. Joe. Joe. Joe. Show us your hand. Show us you don't have the salt in your hand
Yeah, let's see the kelbasa
You know, you're not supposed to eat that raw, right? Yeah, Joe, why did you
Who doesn't eat their cigarette butts? Oh my god, your cigarette butt
Well, do you remember the kelbasa queen from Howard Stern? Can you do what she did?
You members to bond members to bond. Yeah, so I remember her
members use like a guy
Got the wet
Yeah, well he lived in like some like squatted our apartment in like New York and it was really
The not a very passable transsexual
But do you remember when Eric was in school and he was like
Classic one yeah
Yeah, God bless you
Yeah
Okay, Joe you're breaking up can you talk close to your mic or
the
I do have some freedom
You don't know like I said this I kind of my eyes to kind of mean if I just I've rushed resting bitch face
I'm resting bitch face stop
Have like a little frown and
That's why I look all mad all the time. I'm not really not mad
So brush you know you're not mad. You're a god. I love your positive energy psych
Thank you. No
I'm gonna you have a little bit of your eyebrows. I still love you, but I have a what on my eyebrows eyebrows are great
Fuck that is but it's it's infectious. Oh, no, this in the middle. It's a little dense in my head. Oh
Dent okay, I got you
Actually when I had my nose job I had it filled in and it feels in but then it like we're back to normal a little after a little while
Hey Lola do you want to say hi to Joe? Do you want to say hi to Joe Lola? Lola's my resting bitch face, can't you?
Let me say hi, let me say hi, please.
Let me say R.
Look at the green eyes. Look at the eyes, guys. Gorgeous.
Uh, let's see. I found, yeah, so people were talking about uh,
fixing laser 3D printers or something. Let's see.
Yeah
You can actually like you can actually print a gun, you know, get a three to three
I don't know how easy
Comments like really I don't have an hour to waste
It's okay the comments
Really 20,000 comments today, so
Do you change your profile Harry
She I like it. Oh, no, it looks the same. It was that pan is that pan or something that pan who is that in the profile photo or mushroom guy?
How okay, I
Know a lot of people think
Because he's like he went whatever well one time when Robin Quiver said that she got sick
Howard actually almost teared up when he lost Robin for one day because that takes a team to make a show and
Robin and Howard that's a team boys. That's a fucking team. You're talking about
I'll go to my grade with Howard and Robin
Robin Givens. Oh, what's her name?
Robin field. Oh field
the
Mine that is a fine. I
Just say it like this guy's writing you a fucking paragraph. You're tired. It's like you didn't
They're not ready to be the talking the chat to each other, so
They're not laser printers and stuff I don't really understand you gotta stick to three
What's up
You don't even know Kimmy Gibbler's dad's name
Mr. Gibbler
Yeah, I swear to God my answer is gonna be mr. Gibbler. Yeah, mr. Gibbler senior. Yeah, mr. Gibbler. Thank you, psych
Yeah, what do you think I had Harry?
Harry Harry Harry Harry Harry we
Modge has been beating me up over here a little bit
the
Go ahead. Yeah, it's like no repeat it boy. What do you say here?
He's singing the full house theme song
Yeah
Very confusing I love to make a baby
It's like the baby robot hobby robot I asked you
I can't even see
Joe do you consider yourself like a violent drunk, bro?
I don't I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am I am
all
Yep
Yeah, wait, so interesting Joe I got
What are you doing to your ever been called the practical flat they might know they call the rascal flat today. Yeah
Joe Joe did we land on the moon Joe before you came we were talking about landing on the moon Joe
I
Here
I'm turning my camera and guys
How do I fit this? How do I get this out of my ass?
How do I get it in?
I think you might have to get a surgery removed, bro
No, it's just like uh, it's pretty like a little rope at the end of it and uh
you know, pull it out again, just
go, go, go, hop over the fence in the neighbor's yard
and the dog will help you out, don't worry about it
you might have to do a little run-in
Friday, I fault the fence
I get on the fence and hump it
no man, the dog is just gonna eat it out of your ass
don't worry bro, just go
see, see, he's beaver
he's beaver
No, I'm not you fucking asked for how the hell can I get this out of my ass, right?
And you're not being the rude one
No, come on, bro. Like, you know, are you really pulling off fucking leg over here?
My
So listen did we land on the moon
Yeah, we did in 1969. We did wait. All right. So 1969 and a 69 like an ending 99 99 99, right? So
We landed there, but we have telescopes we have telescopes that can see other galaxies, but we can't find the fucking
And we can't find the flag we left that right you have your telescopes that can fucking see across galaxies
Find me the flag they left send me a picture
And I don't want one of these fabricated fucking like go get a telescope
said the fucking you're a man
Pull it up fucking see craters on the moon. So I'm sure you can see a flag
Find me the flag bro, and I'll believe and I'll believe your bullshit. You know what I'm saying
You know
No fool
no fall I don't
anybody that believes we were in there and the moon is on fire
I believe we did land on the moon we're gonna agree to disagree
wow when we can't leave this atmosphere
just the solar flares we're gonna be challenged
you can see the guy's footprint on the moon
and he was wearing Nike so
right
Right Nike, you know
Nike means Nikki right Nikki means win
Let me explain to you a fucking
You know Nike came from the word
You know 300 you know the movie 300 the guy who ran to go tell everybody yo they're fucking coming and to save the rest
You know the guy who ran he ran like a marathon, right?
26 miles right so he ran that shit and then he died at the end
That's what they fucking made the Nikki that was Nikki
you know, and that's when Nike came after that. Look it up.
I brought you. Thank you is from that fucking shit. Yo, Yara.
Well, I'll tell you right now, I don't drop that when I'm on a marathon, but so so we went to the moon.
You're damn right, we did.
How, bro, how when the fucking astronauts themselves don't even he can't get a fucking story straight?
they can't even, they don't even know what to say, and they keep running, they see reporters, they see reporters and they keep running
you're not going to be the first thing that's going to be done
bro, they see reporters and they run
they are like so against being questioned, why?
why is it that we lost the technology to go, like what was so sophisticated that we don't know the technology anymore to go
Look it up. Look it up. Look it up that we don't have the technology to go to fucking moon anymore
But we had it. We don't got no more. We lost though. We destroyed it because
Yeah, I don't know
The fucking
The dog ate it
Tried finding me the information of how to go there. Does it exist? Where is the technology? We have lost
This is the problem that there's a lot of people like you that
There's a lot of people like you that vote, you know that right?
where do you mean a lot of people like me
Well, well, there was there was something Socrates said, you know, or Plato. I don't know one of those fucking retards
Right, right, right. He said that these dumb
Coverin the smart because there's just more of you and then you're
So you guys you know, it's because there's just a lot of more dumb and motherfuckers like you believe in the bullshit
So we're over here. Yo
We're pointing out all the bullshit and you're fucking
Like a home of simpson cracking cans on your fucking, you know on your head to drink them
You just said you poor fucking everywhere else
You know you do look like fucking
What was the sun's name?
Your part all grown up
That's why poor the 14 dollars in my water
That's all
Go get more
You can get another case
We can get another case of Bud Light your favorite shit
I'm a priestess shit, I guess
No, bro, you don't need money money is not
Why why look at all the rich people? They're the worst fucking people on the planet
They're fucking they have nothing to do but uh, you know, they lose it
How much money you got show me show me show me any rich person that is normal show me one
Yo, this fucking guy had this girl shitting on the bed in the divorce. Where was it?
This is the first time Johnny Depp's wife, right Johnny Depp's wife is shitting on his bed
And I got that one time, you know that fucking little bitch
Reminded me of that, you know
Yeah, oh
Reminded me of a little bit
Right
Okay, that's nice
But you know what brought you listen listen, you know like for some reason right when I was a kid
I wouldn't beat up drunk people. I don't know why I just felt
You know, I'm just saying no, you know like when I was a kid
Even even as a grown-up, you know, I don't know why I always give drunk people a pass
I don't know why
What about seeing you? I would knock you the fuck out, but
That's funny, dude, that's what normally a drunk person would say and then they start on and break their face
You know, that's funny. I bet you bet you bet you bet you bet a bit. You bet a bit
You bet a bit. I wouldn't take your money dude. I wouldn't take it
I wouldn't take your money. Come on, bro. You got 17 bucks
I'm telling you
You'll just stumble into the you know, you just stumble and break your face
the
I don't know, good fucking question bro, but how many pieces did they give you?
You remember that commercial when there was like a bird that licked a lollipop?
Like, how many licks?
Well, I would think that you wouldn't know the answer about the fucking beer and asshole shit because you probably
You know done it with your mama, right?
You be in your mama's ass. You be in your mama's ass
In there
So drunk again
Do you do it in front of your daddy
What part of the country you're from?
Do you see corn outside your window?
I'm actually from an article
It article so you see elk and shit outside your window. Oh
Oh saucy fucking albino
What you guys got albinos? Oh
Yeah, man
What does that mean?
Is that is that is that is that the type of is that the only type of black people allowed there are by no black
No, you sound like a racist to me, yo
Why you calling fucking black people up I knows now all of a sudden yo
I think you should stop drinking me
You know, where's my voice a man when I
So basket do you live in bro like the rugged the rugged the rugged pot
You need a four wheeler to get around
of the
the
Oh hell yeah, there's there's functions very
Really, how long does a big moose last?
I'm gonna say one thing don't be but I'll say one animal that is delicious is like if you ever
So you say so you say moose tastes like cat
I'm saying you put a moose in the cat in front of me. I think I'm dipping that cat in barbecue sauce
Yeah
You're gonna eat cats
You know you might be Asian
I'm gonna go that far. God, sir
Can I call you sir?
Yeah, you can call me sir. You can call me God sir. Whatever you want
Did I call you ma'am?
Can I call you ma'am?
ma'am
I mean, I guess if you want, I mean, in the world that we live in today,
I guess you could identify others as whatever you want.
I guess I just did 10 minutes ago with a doggo.
All right, so you could identify me as that, you know.
Oh, well, you want to identify me?
It makes you happy there, you know.
Ain't no day.
As long as it's like it's like he let me up here. Yes, I can do that in fucking here. No other big crack yet
I don't want to fucking kids
You're cheap, thank you, you know
Shut up
You can't even drink or a fake fucking drunk shut up
You're a fake drunk, bro, you fucking can't even drink
Can't believe your drunk and you're a fucking you you crack you have to empty cans over there
Trying to make believe you drunk you fucking idiot. That's exactly what you're doing you're fucking moron
Yeah, please come sir. Please come down. Let's let me pet that cat look at that. Okay. We're working on now
At least we took away from the man. You're not now. You're learning now. You're learning not now
You know you're trying to find
Now you started to find your foot in around me, you know what I'm saying now you're starting to find your foot in
you know you got a little shot over here maybe you got like a nice little a nice little left hook
you know and you're like whoa let me let me let me let me take it easy here you know what i'm
saying we don't know we don't know this one oh you don't know bro i'm the biggest monster
i'm the biggest fucking monster i'll make you fucking think twice about living sorry bad man
You know
Then again, I told you I give
But if I start to think that you're a fake drunk
My god, what's gonna happen to you buddy?
You're right. I see I'm not like every time I come up here. I'm gonna fly
You're a fake drunk. You're a fake drunk. Tell everybody. You're right. It's all an act. I'm a fake drunk. It's all a fucking act.
Boom
We're recording
Good, I got something you record, but what is the point? What is the point? What are you trying to prove by being a fake one?
Why are you trying to prove by fucking coming out here acting drunk?
That was my
of the
that is how rude that's that's most women too for some reason but why do you
think you gingers are always
I'm like you're a woman
all right whatever blah blah blah delusion delusion
okay
okay okay let's look at the statistics let's look at the statistics
Why do women not like fucking redheads for some reason?
Well, I want it. Why is Jim Nick whispered to me with loving boys?
Well, there might be a few of them that leave, you know, you know, but for every far between
Women fucking that are interested in a ginger like you know what I'm saying
What is that your picture yeah one second hi
Hi
So now now now your turn ginger
Go ahead. So I get your panel. Who's like psych psych he's saying for you to say hi
Okay, listen, listen, I didn't think you have anybody but I guess
He might change his mind about the ginger thing. He was just joking
You know
I got him class in his hands
Yeah, but what is it like your finger to yourself like how the fuck is that shit read right?
Why does it come out like that?
You bitch if you're gonna call me a fucking
the
I
Doesn't even care about you. He said he doesn't like redheads with the fuck is wrong with you, bro
You keep fucking they don't get it. I look like they I heard about, you know men like not taking rejection
Well, but you're fucked up, bro
I'm not really going to
the
Let's put crazy like what the fuck is wrong with you?
I'm still waiting to hear listen just put your mother on the phone and let her say hi for you
I'm still waiting to hear some girls say hi. Hi, you know like something I don't know
the
Yeah, dude, I'm not saying you can walk into any fucking movie theater and, you know, it can be black in there, you know, these girls are still gonna see you and they're gonna be like, oh, shit.
It's an asshole.
Got a red cracker up in here, you know what I mean?
You're glowin' a dog, bro.
Shut up.
Just say no.
And it's because you eat a lot of potatoes, you know, they got fuckin' phosphorus in them, so that's why I pay though.
Remember the potato famine?
Yeah, bro. That was hot that happened in fucking Ireland where you're from, right?
Oh, no, let me turn my camera on there. She does
Remember 200 years ago when I was people. Oh, no, let me ask you a question
200 years ago. I was people came from America and now they're normal
member like
No, but listen, bro. Listen, listen, listen. Do you know that your bloodline was the first slaves in America?
English hadn't slaves the fucking listen, bro. Let me educate you man, please
You know the English had fucking enslaved the fucking Irish, you know that right and the Scottish
You know they enslaved them too
they were no fuck about it either
And they brought them over here, and they were the first slaves in America. That's a fact right there that I told you
So you fucking if anybody's gonna get restitution in this country, it should be your white black ass
slave ass
Your slave ass deserves more restitution than anybody cuz you were the first you were the first no
I'm telling you look up history though
Talking about beautiful bro. You're beautiful bro. Don't let anybody tell you anything else man. You're Irish and you're beautiful
You're not asleep sir
You're welcome very much
That's what's up
So tell us man
Did you go to your parade I
Just think you have a crazy. Do you have a parade in Nebraska?
I went through pride parade
boy
I was talking about the Irish one man. Oh
The Irish run I went to that one. Oh
You see but I caught you I caught you there
You and your fucking sausages running around. I'm sure you had a whole bunch tied around your neck. You know what I'm saying
Well, there you took me well, I sure did I sure did
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it,
You know he has his own panel. He waits for people to come up here and fucking say what they want to say
What is he gonna fucking keep repeating himself over and over?
Oh, I'm interesting. How many fucking things you think he has to say?
What is he gonna tell you how many times he's gonna fucking shave the back of his balls a week?
Then how would you do he has to say?
You have nothing to say
Well, well well until what Don and then someone else comes up. They'll have something else to say too
you know
we'll figure out what's wrong with you
I'm rhyming up here today
he said
he don't have anything to say to you
this guy doesn't have anything to say
what do you mean I got too much to say bro
we were just fucking questioning
your fucking mentality about the moon
and you failed
You know what the thing is like a lot of people can talk all day, but like you might have too much to say
But that won't work for you
Stop walking around in your fucking shithole fucking looking for freakin rocks in your carpet stay in one fucking place dickhead
Stay in one place man, you know, you're breaking up bro. You got really bad reception
know what you're fucking Walmart phone
You know I mean
What is that like him with a bunch of lights behind him is that a picture really
Which one you're talking about the one with the blue thing the blue
About you. I'm not right about you, but
What do you mean that blue the one with the lights in the back? What are you talking about the blue lights?
That's not me man. Stop talking about that person like that. It's not nice
It's muted up don't you see that his fucking mic is muted that person's mic is muted. You don't see it
You don't see it
You're fucking drunk and blind now
You know, that's the problem with the fucking red heads. They come outside and they're fucking corny has get burnt by the son
Yes, it's racist racist again all about the red heads see racist
No, bro, I got a family that's red heads. Fuck you talking about
typical little loser race
of the
don't like my dad answers for you
With your question buddy, I have lots of questions. You're just having an answer
Why are you recording? Are you Mexican?
I'm Mexican. I was born man
Hmm. I
Was born in El Paso, Texas. I know so you have Mexican, right?
Thank you. Yeah
Are you thinking you're gonna get deported?
I hope not.
No.
But it's nice in Mexico.
How if I get deported to Harry?
I don't know. Why not?
Why are you an American in there now?
You think you belong here? You're Irish, dude.
Go back to fucking Maryland.
You know, pick fucking Forty Clovers over there
and fucking talk like a fucking leprechaun.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
a lot the people that talk a lot about the guy are probably an employee and I feel like it's obvious
the ones that talk a lot. You'd be like the first Mexican leprechaun, bro.
Well, that's the first Mexican leprechaun. Well, it's so original.
Why, did you ever fucking hear that before? No, I never heard of it before.
All right. All right.
of that
so anyway, so you're not convincing anybody that you're drunk, you know that, right?
so you don't get no pass at all
so what I think I'm trying to do is come to be in juice, I'm drunk
I've got friends argue that
so I'm just saying
so then why show us that you're drinking?
so it's like you're drinking
why show us you're drinking, right?
that's a real man right there, that's a real man
that's a real man
Fuckin' Natty Daddy, boy, that is not true.
Oh, what is that, the bum juice?
Oh, we got some bum juice, that's the ice shit, yeah.
That shit is like 100 proofin' shit, right?
I'll have you fucking spray in the bathroom.
I
Like a minimum you know what I'm saying all that fucking
I was gonna be all over the back of your fucking shower, bro. You know what I'm saying. What's your coffin?
You'll be caught
The bag, you know, I'm saying
Watch that shit
I'm just saying what's gonna I'm just saying bro, you know, you keep fucking drinking that bum juice you'll be fucking
spraying your shot like
What's wrong with being gay over something you're like gay people bro, why are you here then?
Yeah
Why does that don't like gays man, what's wrong with this guy, you know what I'm saying
What's wrong with you, bro? You're the one that doesn't have a girl man. Fuck you dickhead
I bet you're a virgin 100% on this
You are a virgin. I bet you are a virgin. I'm 100% on this one. You're a virgin. You're a virgin.
100%. 100% on that.
You're gonna be a hundred and there's nothing wrong with it. There's nothing wrong with being a virgin
There's a lot of women looking for virgins, bro
You know because most women have a men mentality, you know, and they're like toxic males today
So like the toxic male is that is the modern woman like the toxic male is the modern woman. So I
Think you can find a lot of women for you. They're like a modern woman. Yeah
Then call me call at least show me respect. I'll call you Alicia because you're like more like of a black like
violent drunk like a wig-wearing
Pool again. That's what I'll let you are. Yeah
Okay, that's what you are. Yo, not me. Oh, you're like
You know you present yourself like a black woman, you know, you want your freedom and shit even though you're free
You know, nobody's fucking holding you know where
Shit, you know what I'm saying? Just put your fucking wig on straight. You're fucking drunk and shut up
Now you're talking mr. Big bites you must be
that's
If you didn't fucking work for your pussy, it doesn't count. I don't have a shit. I don't shut up
If you paid for this, it does not count. You're a virgin motherfucker
You know what I'm saying? You don't count
You've never fucked in your life. Have you?
You're a virgin while this be muted me. So I'll be quiet
You're a virgin bro. I am a virgin
Do you pay for it? Oh
I paid
Pay top, but that's the only way it can happen, right?
Hey
What's going on in Nebraska, what do they have up there like more like me and at all type women
Do you think I've heard Nebraska
all of the